<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="h6b384962g5a7bg33e2g8993g0708cacc7834" version="3">Rule: Equipping Weapons</content>
  <content contentuid="h7e686044g6737gd055gea94g27a7a4c34341" version="3">You can equip weapons when you make an attack as part of attack action. Equipping a weapon includes drawing it from a sheath or picking it up.</content>
  <content contentuid="haf418bd4gaf68g349dge3fbg4db2a9970409" version="1">Dodge</content>
  <content contentuid="h40481577g00cege926g9b8cg4479348271b0" version="1">Until the start of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has Disadvantage, and you make Dexterity saving throws with Advantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h77f164a8g908ag78fdg969cg13b085d02634" version="2">If you reach 0 hit points, you fall Unconscious and must make Death Saving Throws. On 3 successes, you stop bleeding out and become Stable. On 3 failures, you die. If you roll a 20 on the d20, you regain 1 Hit Point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you regain any hit points, the condition is removed. If an ally &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Help"&gt;Helps&lt;/LSTag&gt; you, you regain 1 hit point.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd91b86adge685g5c21gf879g457242b186f2" version="2">While you have the Prone condition, you experience the following effects:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restricted Movement: You must spend an amount of movement equal to half your Speed to stand up and end the condition. If your Speed is 0, you can’t stand up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attacks Affected: An attack roll against you has Advantage if the attacker is within [1] of you. Otherwise, that attack roll has Disadvantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d9f934eg7721gfb63gcff8gb411e659dc78" version="1">Rule: One Spell with a Spell Slot per Turn</content>
  <content contentuid="hd3ffb028g9755g52adgf223g4bb289eebf93" version="1">On a turn, you can expend only one spell slot to cast a spell. This rule means you can’t, for example, cast a spell with a spell slot using the Magic action and another one using a Bonus Action on the same turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb60d9b3bg491bg7056g1bd9gc752b67bfd56" version="1">Mastery Properties: Cleave</content>
  <content contentuid="h57100728g823cg76f4g4795g878063b680ae" version="2">If you hit a creature with a melee attack roll using this weapon, you can make a melee attack roll with the weapon against a second creature within [1] of the first that is also within your reach. On a hit, the second creature takes the weapon’s damage, but don’t add your ability modifier to that damage unless that modifier is negative. You can make this extra attack only once per turn.</content>
</contentList>