<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="h6b384962g5a7bg33e2g8993g0708cacc7834" version="3">Rule: Equipping Weapons</content>
  <content contentuid="h7e686044g6737gd055gea94g27a7a4c34341" version="3">You can equip weapons when you make an attack as part of attack action. Equipping a weapon includes drawing it from a sheath or picking it up.</content>
  <content contentuid="haf418bd4gaf68g349dge3fbg4db2a9970409" version="1">Dodge</content>
  <content contentuid="h40481577g00cege926g9b8cg4479348271b0" version="1">Until the start of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has Disadvantage, and you make Dexterity saving throws with Advantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h77f164a8g908ag78fdg969cg13b085d02634" version="2">If you reach 0 hit points, you fall Unconscious and must make Death Saving Throws. On 3 successes, you stop bleeding out and become Stable. On 3 failures, you die. If you roll a 20 on the d20, you regain 1 Hit Point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you regain any hit points, the condition is removed. If an ally &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Help"&gt;Helps&lt;/LSTag&gt; you, you regain 1 hit point.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd91b86adge685g5c21gf879g457242b186f2" version="2">While you have the Prone condition, you experience the following effects:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restricted Movement: You must spend an amount of movement equal to half your Speed to stand up and end the condition. If your Speed is 0, you can’t stand up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attacks Affected: An attack roll against you has Advantage if the attacker is within [1] of you. Otherwise, that attack roll has Disadvantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d9f934eg7721gfb63gcff8gb411e659dc78" version="1">Rule: One Spell with a Spell Slot per Turn</content>
  <content contentuid="hd3ffb028g9755g52adgf223g4bb289eebf93" version="1">On a turn, you can expend only one spell slot to cast a spell. This rule means you can’t, for example, cast a spell with a spell slot using the Magic action and another one using a Bonus Action on the same turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb60d9b3bg491bg7056g1bd9gc752b67bfd56" version="1">Mastery Properties: Cleave</content>
  <content contentuid="h57100728g823cg76f4g4795g878063b680ae" version="2">If you hit a creature with a melee attack roll using this weapon, you can make a melee attack roll with the weapon against a second creature within [1] of the first that is also within your reach. On a hit, the second creature takes the weapon’s damage, but don’t add your ability modifier to that damage unless that modifier is negative. You can make this extra attack only once per turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h240aa2f4g6571ge23eg8142g83ee7b985b8d" version="1">Mastery Properties: Graze</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fbee9aag6abeg6294g3fd8gbeb26ffd19f6" version="1">If your attack roll with this weapon misses a creature, you can deal damage to that creature equal to the ability modifier you used to make the attack roll. This damage is the same type dealt by the weapon, and the damage can be increased only by increasing the ability modifier.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbe460a9gf800gdb75g15bbg2b81a80fe8ab" version="1">Mastery Properties: Nick</content>
  <content contentuid="h84f8977cg06ecg1e31gebd6g21e4b7346121" version="1">When you make an attack with your off-hand weapon, you can make one additional attack as part of that attack. You can make this additional attack only once per turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h64e7021cg8b69g3f60gde38gd59f3cdc5846" version="1">Mastery Properties: Push</content>
  <content contentuid="h694f6a66g0531g98f0ga23eg525e146eb4d7" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon, you can push the creature up to [1] straight away from yourself if it is Large or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="haf74199bg92cbg93dega0fbgebb535603f83" version="1">Mastery Properties: Sap</content>
  <content contentuid="h6846e460g6aecg1e76g52c0g8c751abe8744" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon, that creature has Disadvantage on its next attack roll before the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb839de91gb995ge42eg62b9g1dd41fe4da4b" version="1">Mastery Properties: Slow</content>
  <content contentuid="h7773a857g54d9g0e61gc338g5671eef1378d" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon and deal damage to it, you can reduce its Speed by [1] until the start of your next turn. If the creature is hit more than once by weapons that have this property, the Speed reduction doesn’t exceed [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="ha395ebeag3995g70fage1d7g718229b74f9b" version="1">Mastery Properties: Topple</content>
  <content contentuid="h5af643b9gd1b7g259cg51cegf17292ec2f43" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon, you can force the creature to make a Constitution saving throw (DC 8 plus the ability modifier used to make the attack roll and your Proficiency Bonus). On a failed save, the creature has the Prone condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdfca5f76g305cgff0cg0532gbc6b23ff9367" version="1">Mastery Properties: Vex</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0019ff2g27f5g13abg7a86g646b2f8a1f55" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon and deal damage to the creature, you have Advantage on your next attack roll against that creature before the end of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a51e8b8gf631gf9b1g55bdg6af9de9235ef" version="1">Greataxe, Halberd</content>
  <content contentuid="hfdefde84gd74bg13d6g3599g34e7bc9cbafe" version="1">Glaive, Greatsword</content>
  <content contentuid="h0de5940ag21a0gff32gb8dfg01c84e54f73e" version="1">Dagger, Light Hammer, Sickle, Scimitar</content>
  <content contentuid="h6fd4a879g6dd9g5936gc329gc012af72f9c6" version="1">Greatclub, Pike, Warhammer, Heavy Crossbow</content>
  <content contentuid="h05a1ab8cg6b39gabd2g55c7g3a1f851c31fb" version="1">Mace, Spear, Flail, Longsword, Morningstar, War Pick</content>
  <content contentuid="h53e29765gaf78g1680g5805g24b5594244ac" version="1">Club, Javelin, Light Crossbow, Sling, Longbow, Musket</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ab19fdega28dg1fd1g0de1gc672bac4e6d3" version="2">Quarterstaff, Battleaxe, Maul, Trident</content>
  <content contentuid="hd724f72fgcda8gb6acgb5c4gd95d169dd0b4" version="1">Handaxe, Shortbow, Rapier, Shortsword, Hand Crossbow, Pistol</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e0a316bg6ce3gc18fgb7c0ge96c73d6dfa0" version="1">Weapon Mastery</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c28362ag369agee34gc8d4g6ccec5460b53" version="1">Your training with weapons allows you to use weapon mastery properties.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you reach certain levels in your class, you gain the ability to use the mastery properties of additional weapon types.</content>
  <content contentuid="he54ffab7g9288g792age85bg3fc0a39a63db" version="1">Level 1: Rage</content>
  <content contentuid="ha33a602cg9bb2gec42g889dg5983a5346c84" version="1">You can imbue yourself with a primal power called Rage, a force that grants you extraordinary might and resilience. You can enter it as a Bonus Action if you aren’t wearing Heavy armor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can enter your Rage the number of times shown for your Barbarian level in the Rages column of the Barbarian Features table. You regain one expended use when you finish a Short Rest, and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8abec533g47afgabaag5370ga724a70ed863" version="1">Level 1: Unarmoured Defence</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc1b8fd5g336eg3648g3224g9cae0aaac491" version="1">Level 2: Danger Sense</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6dea583g9359gddf3g2360g74669f67b1a6" version="1">Level 3: Primal Knowledge</content>
  <content contentuid="h860b399bg558cg749fgb64bg707d53758400" version="1">You can channel primal power when you attempt certain tasks. Whenever you make an ability check using Acrobatics, Intimidation, Perception, Stealth, or Survival, you can add your Strength modifier to the roll. When you use this ability, your Strength represents primal power coursing through you, honing your agility, bearing, and senses.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3fa58ccfg135bg7a66g14degc3c8b5bb8261" version="1">Level 5: Fast Movement</content>
  <content contentuid="h7c047839g4177g2aaega022g36a5cb07886a" version="1">Level 7: Feral Instinct</content>
  <content contentuid="h28d4b453gc36cg810egf9e2g1dbff5d018d8" version="1">Level 7: Instinctive Pounce</content>
  <content contentuid="hdb025275gf26dg03dfg7370g4dddf3f0ffb9" version="1">As part of the Bonus Action you take to enter your Rage, you can move up to half your Speed.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6144726g336aga60cg63d6gf6c4bc669e6a" version="1">Level 9: Brutal Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a320da8g90b9g9714ge237g45c9782afbd0" version="1">If you use Reckless Attack, the target takes an extra 1d10 damage of the same type dealt by the weapon or Unarmed Strike, and you can cause one Brutal Strike effect of your choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forceful Blow. The target is pushed [1] straight away from you. You can then move up to half your Speed straight toward the target without provoking Opportunity Attacks.&lt;br&gt;Hamstring Blow. The target’s Speed is reduced by [1] until the start of your next turn. A target can be affected by only one Hamstring Blow at a time—the most recent one.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf41a9d96ge143g36f0g9f1eg51d9ca5a4cee" version="1">Reckless Attack: Forceful Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="hab5f59ebgf7a8g70bag4453g8c9195f80563" version="1">The target is pushed [1] straight away from you. You can then move up to half your Speed straight toward the target without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebd8f833g052cg4774g5e19geb34be606a5f" version="1">Reckless Attack: Hamstring Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="h0eff4b2bgeb61g4e62ga1ffg3b4f777317e1" version="1">The target’s Speed is reduced by [1] until the start of your next turn. A target can be affected by only one Hamstring Blow at a time—the most recent one.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2fea2840g0902gdf2bg7797g549c20c3d6e3" version="1">Forceful Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd10eb1fgc367ga39egd371g5e071e079549" version="1">You can move up to half your Speed straight toward the target without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5311cf0g6f4fg9a03g45f9gf5ba41e2994c" version="1">Hamstring Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="hcba666bcgdd43g5b9agef09gdcfd2c3d20ff" version="1">The Speed is reduced by [1] until the start of attacker's next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebad3866ga362g915cge97fg661e8b92ea36" version="1">Level 11: Relentless Rage</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd45d1c1g9dd3g206agfb7eg456c6af02ac0" version="1">Once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;, when you would drop to [1] &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; while &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="RAGE"&gt;Enraged&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you instead regain hit points equal to twice your Barbarian level and avoid being &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DOWNED"&gt;Downed&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h784061e1gf2a8g748bg99cfg9e391dd4569c" version="1">Level 3: Frenzy</content>
  <content contentuid="hd21b5d53gc033g82abgfcdag21730bb83c68" version="1">If you use Reckless Attack while your Rage is active, you deal extra damage to the first target you hit on your turn with a Strength-based attack. To determine the extra damage, roll a number of d6s equal to your Rage Damage bonus, and add them together. The damage has the same type as the weapon or Unarmed Strike used for the attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f8570c9g2cd6g2327g3c99g18d5c393bf5e" version="1">Level 6: Mindless Rage</content>
  <content contentuid="h42189866g05d1g89b4g6e9dg1f97d248b2a9" version="1">Level 10: Retaliation</content>
  <content contentuid="hde644cc1g1dc6g103bg095ege867e6fa22ad" version="1">When you take damage from a creature that is within [1] of you, you can take a Reaction to make one melee attack against that creature, using a weapon or an Unarmed Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc8de1446g6777ge942g7572g5cd9d6cc8f14" version="1">Boot of the Giants</content>
  <content contentuid="hf411e734g4162g32ddg2c68g075dce673ed3" version="1">Try to kick a target away. Your chances depend on your Athletics, and are higher if you're hidden or invisible.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5acf268bg7a2dgd7c7g4d2dg20caffe2e8a4" version="1">You can kick targets up to twice the weight that &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Shove"&gt;Shoving&lt;/LSTag&gt; them would allow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e7ef600g82aegeba0g077eg2ddad69731f8" version="1">Surrounded by a barbarian's wild magic. Your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; increases by an amount equal to your Rage Damage bonus until your &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="RAGE"&gt;Rage&lt;/LSTag&gt; ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd75d1783g8062gae55g78a6g651f55455f7f" version="1">Level 2: Jack of All Trades</content>
  <content contentuid="h6002075bg4feegb25ag03b5g8e88a4351c0f" version="1">Level 5: Font of Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="h5d1b01ffgd776g8ca4gd2edgb4e5e0068ad7" version="1">In addition, you can expend a spell slot (no action required) to regain one expended use of Bardic Inspiration.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3c4853cag177dg4ea8g0c15gde7e940ee735" version="1">Font of Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="h7c14769cg0f8ag7968g4156g1272fd5b7850" version="3">Expend a spell slot to regain one expended use of Bardic Inspiration.</content>
  <content contentuid="he36b3403gbab9gf77fg17fbg32e95953478c" version="1">Level 7: Countercharm</content>
  <content contentuid="h1dedae79g3922gbd27g0925g98aec4318fa7" version="1">You can use musical notes or words of power to disrupt mind-influencing effects. If you or a creature within 30 feet of you fails a saving throw against an effect that applies the Charmed or Frightened condition, you can take a Reaction to cause the save to be rerolled, and the new roll has Advantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf8844bacg4eb3geecdg5fbagf17d5ba9d6b0" version="1">Countercharm</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f358bf7g4a10gc77fg43cfg0c187137ef7a" version="1">You can use musical notes or words of power to disrupt mind-influencing effects. If you or a creature within 30 feet of you fails a saving throw against an effect that applies the Charmed or Frightened condition, you can take a Reaction to cause the save to be rerolled, and the new roll has Advantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3169b2acg5134gbc8dge8fagb01eabf3a278" version="1">Level 3: Beguiling Magic</content>
  <content contentuid="h035b29c1g51d0ge9f8gb63fgc75cd5045b0c" version="2">You always have the Charm Person and Mirror Image spells prepared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, immediately after you cast an Enchantment or Illusion spell using a spell slot, you can cause a creature you can see within [1] of yourself to make a Wisdom saving throw against your spell save DC. On a failed save, the target has the Charmed or Frightened condition (your choice) for 1 minute</content>
  <content contentuid="he30a14f7gb323g888eg2ff5g04b0a7374497" version="1">Beguiling Magic: Charmed</content>
  <content contentuid="haac5a803g73dfg5282g175eg12c90e9a77cd" version="1">Beguiling Magic: Frightend</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e9e444agc6b5g3056g6b60g447875f0ec07" version="1">Level 3: Mantle of Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="hd68a192ag408cg0b94ge1bcgb6efd87c7b6a" version="2">You can weave fey magic into a song or dance to fill others with vigor. As a Bonus Action, you can expend one use of Bardic Inspiration and roll your Bardic Inspiration die. When you do so, choose a number of other creatures within [1] of yourself, up to your Charisma modifier (minimum of one creature).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h719facf1g5f1cg71c4gbf18g0bc0200d571d" version="2">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd927a3dfg462bg2162g0ddegc1f29c11bb86" version="1">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3f5c8f9g2b3bg1058g7715gee2645709a64" version="1">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h52a153aag53d8g2658g72aegc55c7baffc11" version="1">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h530230d7ge34cg06b9g06a3ge16228b8a608" version="1">Creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcc01542ag2ea8ge230g53b5g6bae54a352d2" version="1">Level 3: Cutting Words</content>
  <content contentuid="hfac955c9g640eg8dc8gfdefgfa559fa195f8" version="2">Level 6: Extra Attack (Cantrip)</content>
  <content contentuid="he6112d47g8846ge668gbd97g45ddd36eeb46" version="1">You can attack twice instead of once whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, you can cast one of your cantrips that has a casting time of an action in place of one of those attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1a1b446eg2636gca22g7bafg910726511c02" version="1">Aid</content>
  <content contentuid="h5380e85fg27eagff54gaa61g803d6710929e" version="1">Choose up to three creatures within range. Each target’s Hit Point maximum and current Hit Points increase by [1] for the duration.</content>
  <content contentuid="he6319c8dga9bagd985gfc80gc057d99c3f06" version="1">Aid</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c0c79e8geefage313gb534gd315de67d298" version="1">Increase your allies' hit point maximum by [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="hbdf4d91ege560gf373gb78fgc694716131ec" version="1">Word of Radiance</content>
  <content contentuid="h0dd0eba8g9b93g7909g9d9cg2a09e01a4c46" version="2">Level 1: Divine Order: Protector</content>
  <content contentuid="h82c38cb3g39e6g13c8g7a26g5c63f737aa79" version="1">Protector: Trained for battle, you gain proficiency with Martial weapons and training with Heavy armor.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd91012edgb1a6g4aabg14d4g0d685464de55" version="1">Thaumaturge: You know one extra cantrip from the Cleric spell list. In addition, your mystical connection to the divine gives you a bonus to your Intelligence (Arcana or Religion) checks. The bonus equals your Wisdom modifier (minimum of +1).</content>
  <content contentuid="h5eae110bgf170g8febg7b95gaf9957eab275" version="1">Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="hf42e4215gdaa7g8b2cg6d6cg34b3a7233576" version="1">Light</content>
  <content contentuid="h08e84982gdf0fgadf1g29d5g02cc8281827c" version="2">Bursting Sinew</content>
  <content contentuid="hf2980afegb1f3g08e3g5b30g296c1e8141b7" version="1">Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h3dc64960ga68egb106gddd9g8a83f2e5394a" version="1">Sacred Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="h37124d24g1b0dg1b86g632dg14623f5d21b6" version="1">Spare the Dying</content>
  <content contentuid="h31c6269fga1bfge0a9gb4bfg7f845b81b38a" version="1">Thaumaturgy</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d2d81f9g6a4cg493ege377gd246536aefa0" version="1">Toll the Dead</content>
  <content contentuid="h5d663b96gee20gd7abg28bdgde325d686903" version="1">Divine Order</content>
  <content contentuid="hf078c843g4ca9gd89bgde69g7b94c3d7e9b4" version="1">You have dedicated yourself to one of the following sacred roles of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc0f7da49g83b0g2364gd22fg0e72e6d0f671" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Word of Radiance</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d5b8b7cg1eddg15a0g6e0cgb4e68f50ee06" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="h865f785bge303g1b8ag2f0egee91191a55fd" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Light</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bfe486dga99eg5aefg818agacd35ff6e130" version="2">Level 1: Divine Order: Bursting Sinew</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5ac78c8g2d8cg02bag6ebbg2f9ccd67bc36" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h63c03147gca42g60bdgfa7ag47ceb695bc38" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Sacred Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="hf2f5e5c4g141ag2b8egb90cg9ff6727b6910" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Spare the Dying</content>
  <content contentuid="h50136471gff21g505fg888cgf856fc01281a" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Thaumaturgy</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b0eeaeeg6a13gc99dg6669gc97c57ec0db5" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Toll the Dead</content>
  <content contentuid="h84a7d362gf65ag0f66g6103g7d1f4fc707d2" version="1">Level 2: Channel Divinity</content>
  <content contentuid="h619804afg28a4g6f48g9db2gb39ec7c1d073" version="1">You can channel divine energy to create special effects such as Divine Spark and Turn Undead, choosing one each time you use Channel Divinity. Additional effects and uses are gained at higher Cleric levels. You regain one use on a Short Rest and all uses on a Long Rest. Saving throw DCs use your Spellcasting DC.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fdb1f5ag867fg21d4g6beeg681eae4df812" version="1">Divine Spark</content>
  <content contentuid="he5c89bffgb42ege4daga349g64ec3fecb28f" version="1">As a Magic action, you point your Holy Symbol at another creature you can see within [1] of yourself and focus divine energy at it. You either restore Hit Points to the creature or force the creature to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, the creature takes Necrotic or Radiant damage (your choice). On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage (round down).</content>
  <content contentuid="h49ee25b5g5f2age7acga266g96075d1e4240" version="1">Divine Spark: Heal</content>
  <content contentuid="hbcd0c295g2003g99d5ge6fcg5fad76be07bb" version="1">You restore Hit Points to a creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b82bf91ge1b7g4b75g2472g3c3dbf201a2d" version="1">Divine Spark: Radiant Damage</content>
  <content contentuid="hb95127abg79cag5782ge868geb1002d62c1c" version="1">You deal damage to a creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9db3b3abg7a4dg3f7fg42a9g43591b76887d" version="1">Divine Spark: Necrotic Damage</content>
  <content contentuid="hb1119630g31c7g738eg4a76g56eb77fe86bc" version="1">Level 7: Blessed Strikes: Divine Strike (Radiant)</content>
  <content contentuid="hb14ca27eg593ag392fgab27g2186f2a37316" version="2">Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with an attack roll using a weapon, you can cause the target to take an extra [1]</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5f17982g16bdg018bg655eg1db1622f5096" version="1">Level 7: Blessed Strikes: Divine Strike (Necrotic)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd61761e0gbebfg6542gac8bgd70ab3faa548" version="1">Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with an attack roll using a weapon, you can cause the target to take an extra 1d8 Necrotic.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbdc1e3fg886agebc7gf898gdd7b5aea06a3" version="1">Level 7: Blessed Strikes: Potent Spellcasting</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d199d0egf3a1ga886gf931gb46f01ab73e5" version="1">Potent Spellcasting. Add your Wisdom modifier to the damage you deal with any Cleric cantrip.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4bebd04fg3a81gc270gd50bga237aecd8ef8" version="1">Blessed Strikes</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c4d3581gf44cg6a9ag27f8ge9f2dd54d6ed" version="1">Divine power infuses you in battle. You gain one of the following options of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6ac0f1cg84d4g5137g1a23g92f5941f06dc" version="1">Level 5: Sear Undead</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9e8561fg5920g7f26g9d66g15b2d44e24f3" version="1">Spare the Dying</content>
  <content contentuid="hb742b3aagabfcg536cg10e0g99bbe354e49a" version="1">Heal a creature within range that has 0 Hit Points and isn’t dead.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd085b0deg3cc9g0858gdf14geef98a4164c3" version="1">Word of Radiance</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb7ccd06g2737gdcf2gc167g21f32c9615fb" version="1">Burning radiance erupts from you in a [1] Emanation. Each creature of your choice that you can see in it must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf652a768gef39g78fdg661dg8ddbb887d3f3" version="1">Level 3: Disciple of Life</content>
  <content contentuid="h748a060egc16cg7d82gf97eg22830dd0c9f1" version="1">When a spell you cast with a spell slot restores Hit Points to a creature, that creature regains additional Hit Points on the turn you cast the spell. The additional Hit Points equal 2 plus the spell slot’s level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h45db170cgfec9gad8eg1591gd99ec7aa2b2c" version="1">Level 6: Blessed Healer</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f58f448gfe00g1b2agab56g46c8bf14ca5f" version="1">The healing spells you cast on others heal you as well. Immediately after you cast a spell with a spell slot that restores Hit Points to one or more creatures other than yourself, you regain Hit Points equal to 2 plus the spell slot’s level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae1dce65g444ag6a6egf7d3g354c47c64531" version="1">Preserve Life</content>
  <content contentuid="hf73a03f1g9a62g7708g6ac9ge3ea9b45c4a8" version="1">As a Magic action, you present your Holy Symbol and expend a use of your Channel Divinity to evoke healing energy that can restore a number of Hit Points equal to five times your Cleric level. Choose Bloodied creatures within [1] of yourself (which can include you), and divide those Hit Points among them.</content>
  <content contentuid="haed19d90g7118gfa81g42d5gba4d717eba4c" version="1">Blooded</content>
  <content contentuid="h28bdf1edg1a62gc8a2gc601gdedb4f01f3b6" version="1">This creature’s Hit Points have dropped below 50%.</content>
  <content contentuid="h12e63398gc863ged08g09d8g9e2fffc91af3" version="1">Channel Divinity</content>
  <content contentuid="h62870381g3b8dgbb2cgfc78gf6ba26bd778f" version="1">The number of times you can channel your divine powers.</content>
  <content contentuid="h39b48f39g9a41g2ba3g3567g7ab1cb265f82" version="1">Level 3: Warding Flare</content>
  <content contentuid="ha7d55e66g6f97ga4b7g45b4g5829f0c36910" version="2">When a creature that you can see within [1] of yourself makes an attack roll, you can take a Reaction to impose Disadvantage on the attack roll, causing light to flare before it hits or misses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h67f1e6b2g8adcge989g555ag3cbae9d62375" version="1">Level 6: Improved Warding Flare</content>
  <content contentuid="hcac62cb2g678dgbdc4g4a80g875b53ed7a48" version="1">You regain all expended uses of your Warding Flare when you finish a Short or Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, whenever you use Warding Flare, you can give the target of the triggering attack a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to 2d6 plus your Wisdom modifier.</content>
  <content contentuid="h772e3772g49fdg8cf4g0f02g893153584b30" version="1">Warding Flare</content>
  <content contentuid="h6c1ab5a0g8a40g1755g2eacg01f53db2903f" version="1">When a creature that you can see within 30 feet of yourself makes an attack roll, you can take a Reaction to impose Disadvantage on the attack roll, causing light to flare before it hits or misses.</content>
  <content contentuid="h03dc1992g1d8agc3e0ga6bbg22607e81d966" version="1">Warding Flare (Ally)</content>
  <content contentuid="hcb0f1d4dg6ea8gf1eag5e72g32b56f306af2" version="1">Warding Flare (Self)</content>
  <content contentuid="hdc4e30afg0702g20ddgf4a5g1751c8b46770" version="1">Level 3: Invoke Duplicity</content>
  <content contentuid="h31748432g34ebg740cgf353g2071d6cae486" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you can expend one use of your Channel Divinity to create a perfect visual illusion of yourself in an unoccupied space you can see within [1]. The illusion lasts for 1 minute. As a Bonus Action, you can move the illusion up to [1] to another unoccupied space you can see.</content>
  <content contentuid="h002b7ed0g2d07g9ecbg0301g13b767a04c7e" version="1">Level 6: Trickster’s Transposition</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d5766b9g0e51g3888g5633gd570f3096a0f" version="1">Whenever you take the Bonus Action to create or move the illusion of your Invoke Duplicity, you can teleport, swapping places with the illusion.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha73b8276g56b2g1bdegc73bgf16610d268ab" version="1">Trickster’s Transposition</content>
  <content contentuid="h82f58797g491fg0f3ag42b4g05c22ee9679d" version="1">Whenever you take the Bonus Action to create or move the illusion of your Invoke Duplicity, you can teleport, swapping places with the illusion.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5220d58g095fg5ae1g7115g72d15a96ef0c" version="1">You can supernaturally inspire others through words, music, or dance. This inspiration is represented by your Bardic Inspiration die, which is a d6.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using Bardic Inspiration. As a Bonus Action, you can inspire another creature within 60 feet of yourself who can see or hear you. That creature gains one of your Bardic Inspiration dice. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once within the next hour when the creature fails a D20 Test, the creature can roll the Bardic Inspiration die and add the number rolled to the d20, potentially turning the failure into a success. A Bardic Inspiration die is expended when it’s rolled.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number of Uses. You can confer a Bardic Inspiration die a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Higher Levels. Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain Bard levels, as shown in the Bardic Die column of the Bard Features table. The die becomes a d8 at level 5, a d10 at level 10, and a d12 at level 15.</content>
  <content contentuid="h63129871gfb37gc314g1fdfg9b10303bcc26" version="1">Level 1: Bardic Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="h2810e8cag53f2gddb2gb1bbg7d5f6848ec0b" version="1">You can supernaturally inspire others through words, music, or dance. This inspiration is represented by your Bardic Inspiration die, which is a d6.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using Bardic Inspiration. As a Bonus Action, you can inspire another creature within 60 feet of yourself who can see or hear you. That creature gains one of your Bardic Inspiration dice. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once within the next hour when the creature fails a D20 Test, the creature can roll the Bardic Inspiration die and add the number rolled to the d20, potentially turning the failure into a success. A Bardic Inspiration die is expended when it’s rolled.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number of Uses. You can confer a Bardic Inspiration die a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Higher Levels. Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain Bard levels, as shown in the Bardic Die column of the Bard Features table. The die becomes a d8 at level 5, a d10 at level 10, and a d12 at level 15.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e25c63eg08ebg12a0gfefega65d73c0d540" version="1">Level 3: War Priest</content>
  <content contentuid="h04fd168age75cg9dadgeb9bgce0ceddefc4c" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you can make one attack with a weapon or an Unarmed Strike. You can use this Bonus Action a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a Short or Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3c0eb0ffga3ccgcf65g862bg01f7c36b74b8" version="1">War Priest</content>
  <content contentuid="h8686f980g14cdg48cdg0923g21540c804c00" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you can make one attack with a weapon or an Unarmed Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ea2f219gec23g1a96ga5efgce5d1bc88951" version="1">War Priest Extra Attack Charge(s)</content>
  <content contentuid="ha96c97feg6fd1gc562g799fgde13a4800459" version="1">Point used to gain an extra attack as a bonus action.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4dc018cagbaa3ga624g7da2g0a6dab9353ce" version="1">Level 3: Guided Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="ha052e514g0261g1570g0745g00d44f89cc3d" version="1">When you or a creature within 30 feet of you misses with an attack roll, you can expend one use of your Channel Divinity and give that roll a +10 bonus, potentially causing it to hit. When you use this feature to benefit another creature’s attack roll, you must take a Reaction to do so.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81ab1ec4g5097gf34cg7f12g4d040607771b" version="1">Guided Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h900f0f0bgcd61g0708g6d02gf89738f718de" version="1">Level 6: War God’s Blessing</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c6d3ec2g7683g7e9fg7d62g08a6874b3c5f" version="1">You can expend a use of your Channel Divinity to cast Shield of Faith or Spiritual Weapon rather than expending a spell slot. When you cast either spell in this way, the spell doesn’t require Concentration. Instead the spell lasts for 1 minute, but it ends early if you cast that spell again, have the Incapacitated condition, or die.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3bb1c07ag3913g5b74g9454gdcebc7737556" version="1">Shield of Faith: War God’s Blessing</content>
  <content contentuid="hcaeae1ebgf2c5gb598g6716gb1b7c699916c" version="1">Spiritual Weapon: War God’s Blessing</content>
  <content contentuid="h002f5e57g1181g2dbbg226fgf29f606b801c" version="1">Steel Wind Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h0da58492g230cg424fg00cdg006fb672dd4d" version="1">You flourish the weapon used in the casting and then vanish to strike like the wind. Choose up to five creatures you can see within range. Make a melee spell attack against each target. On a hit, a target takes [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h84a10acdg5e1fgb4f6g3b55g7f5134f52d10" version="1">Mind Spike</content>
  <content contentuid="h05f1c3ebg02fcg677cga473g464cac2d584f" version="1">You drive a spike of psionic energy into the mind of one creature you can see within range. The target makes a Wisdom saving throw, taking Psychic damage on a failed save or half as much damage on a successful one. On a failed save, you also always know the target’s location until the spell ends. While you have this knowledge, the target can’t become hidden from you, and if it has the Invisible condition, it gains no benefit from that condition against you.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd666f94dg1a88g5b93g7dcbgfbc951360305" version="1">Synaptic Static</content>
  <content contentuid="haddaa3c4ga780gc6c0g5533g2da826d6931f" version="1">You cause psychic energy to erupt at a point within range. Each creature in a  [1] radius Sphere centered on that point makes an Intelligence saving throw, taking Psychic damage on a failed save or half as much damage on a successful one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a failed save, a target also has muddled thoughts for 1 minute. During that time, it subtracts 1d6 from all its attack rolls and ability checks, as well as any Constitution saving throws to maintain Concentration. The target makes an Intelligence saving throw at the end of each of its turns, ending the effect on itself on a success.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc29da1ffgb5d5g29c2g97c3g2050946f5a23" version="1">Mind Spike</content>
  <content contentuid="h3aac9e83g2f2ag85ddgcf84ge7224ea85b8b" version="1">The creature’s location is always known to the spellcaster until the spell ends. The creature can’t hide from the spellcaster, and if it has the Invisible condition, it gains no benefit from that condition against the spellcaster.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0eb6a1ccg061cg7757g2ce7gb1ae17ae8a0f" version="1">Synaptic Static</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e56e88cg0481g2c87g52e7g140df577385c" version="1">The creature subtracts 1d6 from all its attack rolls and ability checks, as well as from any Constitution saving throws it makes to maintain Concentration. At the end of each of its turns, the target makes an Intelligence saving throw, ending the effect on a success.</content>
  <content contentuid="h32658116g9dc9g1364g0f58g311a9cad82b8" version="1">Level 3: Mind Magic</content>
  <content contentuid="h2035dcdeg7b97g47a9gcfb1gb7bc1f9c6cb9" version="2">As a Magic action, you can expend one use of your Channel Divinity to manifest your magical knowledge. Choose one spell from the Knowledge Domain or the Divination school. As part of the same action, you cast the chosen spell without expending a spell slot.</content>
  <content contentuid="h75bd2293g6a4eg35b3g4781gf184d224ea59" version="1">Level 6: Unfettered Mind</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd98d6aage020gf00bgcd6fg4be2ad2fd956" version="1">You gain proficiency in Intelligence saving throws.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add half of your Wisdom Modifier to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Ability Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; that you are not &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficient&lt;/LSTag&gt; in.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf5d6de51g8683g514bgcfd2gd52016de99fe" version="1">Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="h9cbc738dgd21bg77f4g2687gd1ac412ca2b4" version="1">You launch a mote of light at one creature or object within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes Radiant damage, and until the end of your next turn, it emits Dim Light in a [1] radius and can’t benefit from the Invisible condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d4e8665g6567g3bc4gd9f1g206db8efad20" version="1">Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="he44a89e4gd251g9a1dg6abagca1e9807a226" version="1">The creature emits Dim Light in a [1] radius and can’t benefit from the Invisible condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d4a4bb1g65b7g5025g4514gdfa80f1282ba" version="1">Thunderclap</content>
  <content contentuid="h853f3b07gf693g964eg9f97g97a2cfda50ef" version="1">Each creature in a [1] Emanation originating from you must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take Thunder damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd2e3aa0g3258g4710g9504gbadee9cd0ea6" version="1">Level 1: Druidic</content>
  <content contentuid="h59f8cb26gc1aag4dc3g0939ge1b311504647" version="1">You know Druidic, the secret language of Druids. While learning this ancient tongue, you also unlocked the magic of communicating with animals; you always have the Speak with Animals spell prepared.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1193aa13ge0d7ge702g2f85ga0c0527d229d" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Warden</content>
  <content contentuid="h236eb2e6g63d1g6008gac03gd13912a2af7b" version="1">Warden. Trained for battle, you gain proficiency with Martial weapons and training with Medium armor.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdc66e2feg6dc9g8e0dg69c3g1ac135e77240" version="1">Level 1: Primal Order: Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="h261201bdgf3e1gc0a9g001bg9f21c4b6eb0b" version="1">Magician. You know one extra cantrip from the Druid spell list. In addition, your mystical connection to nature gives you a bonus to your Intelligence (Arcana or Nature) checks. The bonus equals your Wisdom modifier (minimum bonus of +1).</content>
  <content contentuid="hf498864agc7beg3cdbgca11g269c576f1a01" version="1">Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e0c0b74gabceg8644g0a67g8c877d23dd83" version="1">Level 1: Primal Order: Poison Spray</content>
  <content contentuid="h3635dadfgfe4eg55c4g39dfgaf968256d2d8" version="1">Poison Spray</content>
  <content contentuid="h5307ff13g4736g2ce2ga66fg11f20a990de2" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Produce Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="h5169409cg04adgc907gd30eg09ebe8d3738c" version="1">Produce Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="h55c47b09ga380g8cf2g15b8g2bedd46fe8e9" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h69ae862bga7a4g2605g04a4gd9317e169763" version="1">Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0c364a3g050eg598bgd2fdg4c1b525be149" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Shillelagh</content>
  <content contentuid="h599263a1g8987g0f3dgf199g149b6068247f" version="1">Shillelagh</content>
  <content contentuid="hab8ea7d9g7419g79d4ge012g86380a295a02" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: SpareTheDying</content>
  <content contentuid="hf5a7c07dg5d75g8b41g3ce4g8e350dae85b9" version="1">SpareTheDying</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5bb58c8g9203g4533gc615ga31bea2a2187" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="h8891553bg7ca5g791ag4b95g5a72f6e71ed4" version="1">Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="hc7a0905fg5836g8050gb036gd435c6a53ffd" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Thorn Whip</content>
  <content contentuid="h1793f9fbgf70agf3acge48bg70b646b51326" version="1">Thorn Whip</content>
  <content contentuid="h566f5dd1g1db3g0d0age62cg0ff1909892ef" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Thunderclap</content>
  <content contentuid="hf81ea6f0gb2bcg2e34g72c5gfeb99fd56826" version="1">Thunderclap</content>
  <content contentuid="ha16fbd5eg7072g66aeg7f0eg739d38d2a607" version="1">Primal Order</content>
  <content contentuid="h22f70fd0g4354g1c46g6712gdc288b7803e5" version="1">You have dedicated yourself to one of the following sacred roles of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb670c3bdg0b18g5834g24e2gce9406adf925" version="1">Wild Shape Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e2c2a49gb8a7g78d8gf687gb0cdc6987be7" version="1">The number of times you can use your Wild Shape.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f1b692bg604cgb34cg9e64g7c5d22aebe85" version="1">Level 2: Wild Shape</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6dea6aag9290gf3cegeb8ag0351bd8d0fc5" version="2">You can use a Bonus Action to transform into a known Beast form using Wild Shape. You can end the transformation early as a Bonus Action. You can use Wild Shape twice. You regain one expended use when you finish a Short Rest, and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest. When you assume a Wild Shape form, you gain a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to your Druid level. You can’t cast spells, but shape-shifting doesn’t break your Concentration or otherwise interfere with a spell you’ve already cast.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1505dff7gb11cg17eageb5dg29f041ed571a" version="1">Level 2: Wild Shape</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e8ebc40g6f5cg5d29gc885g2f7fb0f2899b" version="1">Wild Shape</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e1bf345gb5fcg3bbag17c4g7ac514e8455e" version="1">When you assume a Wild Shape form, you gain a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to your Druid level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8a519044g61f3g7166g3e0cg6c97799602e4" version="1">Wild Shape: Badger</content>
  <content contentuid="h9c56ac47g3984g90a8g0115g3a3000abd94a" version="1">Wild Shape: Polar Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h55c8bb9fgab04g0e14gce66g6d7734c64973" version="1">Wild Shape: Cat</content>
  <content contentuid="h4bd8abf4gf0adgc66cgc5bag97c641b5e998" version="1">Wild Shape: Deep Rothé</content>
  <content contentuid="hb0d5b816gde08g18fag0b3dg87d87c0c5144" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Raven</content>
  <content contentuid="h5290eb7agca74g04fdg1c90gf56091132a96" version="1">Wild Shape: Giant Spider</content>
  <content contentuid="h78df260fgc265gf45fg5e7eg3a5e3f320112" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d5751c2gc7e1ge1c7g2187gc1dfba8f54e2" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="hfad853e7g6d71gc847gc4e1g6c0f425eab30" version="1">Wild Shape: Badger</content>
  <content contentuid="h94425109g11ccg2387g6f3ag6e092535cfc7" version="1">Wild Shape: Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h125b5a75g4894g085age46age0c6df5c916e" version="1">Wild Shape: Black Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="hc5ea7296g02acg34fdgfa7ag6fdba9447454" version="1">Wild Shape: Grey Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h57fcc347g64cfgce00g9684gdc1711bf0132" version="1">Wild Shape: Polar Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="hb16c19a4gbaaege05bg81b8g91dc2a6ce3ba" version="1">Wild Shape: Boar</content>
  <content contentuid="h5ea20feag7ba3g2debga31dg2a7068efca9a" version="1">Wild Shape: Deep Rothé</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a2047d4g2ebbg73b4gae60g085e395a05a1" version="1">Wild Shape: Spider</content>
  <content contentuid="h43604180gb8bag2721g1fb6g15bf4761d06f" version="1">Wild Shape: Rat</content>
  <content contentuid="h2478c66ag72fbg9200g36ecga9a3f81bd052" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Raven</content>
  <content contentuid="head73bd1g04bfg7aedgaa38g5e91178238da" version="1">Wild Shape: Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h356d9ca7gde59g20cdg3b43g5d69b5e91166" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9efa391g3349g9633gd775ge547b21394a6" version="1">Wild Shape: Sabre-Toothed Tiger</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4e0bdf5g2bedgdb25gd9c5ge125ee988248" version="1">Wild Shape: Panther</content>
  <content contentuid="h4a06421fg399bge851g94a3gc50cf5ac4685" version="1">Wild Shape: Dilophosaurus</content>
  <content contentuid="h98a60dc7g4df3g01fbg8fd5g832b47cc24aa" version="1">Wild Shape: Owlbear</content>
  <content contentuid="h4171bc8fg8509g75b1g344ag4875cb305165" version="1">Wild Shape: Air Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd2efd2eag8f2ag8c20g6458g2d2ee404e737" version="1">Wild Shape: Earth Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="ha20f8cafgc437g2e56ga015ge90f46a9fa2e" version="1">Wild Shape: Fire Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1247016g50d4g5313gc5d9g817268c918e1" version="1">Wild Shape: Water Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="hdcc80e1bg50d8g4d7egf3c5gd88613415b9a" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fbca55age4a4g5797ga82fge26fc359b66c" version="1">Wild Shape: Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h4838ee09g3746g4dc0g2baeg7a9ddd9bf1d4" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Raven</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a5396efg111ag7d25gf58fgce2d27775b14" version="1">Wild Shape: Rat</content>
  <content contentuid="h82d61545g3d50gbd71gb81cg49ba5440aca5" version="1">Wild Shape: Spider</content>
  <content contentuid="he834ae45gcae8gf3bag6df2ga3f6b92b7407" version="1">Wild Shape: Deep Rothé</content>
  <content contentuid="h434d69begc8f3gbd6cg78e1gc7b1896221ee" version="1">Wild Shape: Boar</content>
  <content contentuid="h5cdd815bge132g3d37gdabfg758fee1fd2ff" version="1">Wild Shape: Polar Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h267295feg37f1gf983g6cedg02a6401df1fd" version="1">Wild Shape: Grey Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="hd15c9166gcb1dg4177g3646gbdb76e9200cc" version="1">Wild Shape: Black Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d42344bg665dge300g935bg0d9887bee468" version="1">Wild Shape: Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h59a5a380g59f1gfdb0g9a4fgef72e80eb679" version="1">Wild Shape: Badger</content>
  <content contentuid="h556b4fb3g5a97gb81cg3f21gd57ac1f02a0d" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="h978ef6fag7931g203cg08ccge7b0c344b3e8" version="1">Level 3: Circle Forms</content>
  <content contentuid="h69bf3828g083cg1e10g408egf0f2ee4c7fe8" version="1">You can channel lunar magic when you assume a Wild Shape form, granting you the benefits below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armor Class: Until you leave the form, your AC equals 13 plus your Wisdom modifier if that total is higher than the Beast’s AC.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temporary Hit Points: You gain a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to three times your Druid level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h50a84c2agc47eg3409gfbf3g8b9efe860b49" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Potent Spellcasting</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbacd095g40f6g7468g5750g2f164c7506d4" version="1">Potent Spellcasting. Add your Wisdom modifier to the damage you deal with any Druid cantrip.</content>
  <content contentuid="h623803a7gceadgfb71gf1d2g9f3e3921f3f2" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Cold)</content>
  <content contentuid="h1cfad235g00bdg10bfgf085g60ac289d2534" version="1">Primal Strike. Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with an attack roll using a weapon or a Beast form’s attack in Wild Shape, you can cause the target to take an extra [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="he3035afbgf846g4686gf4e6gc39575739bed" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Fire)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0a6f226g6b60g6204gb543g086832d392ff" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Lightning)</content>
  <content contentuid="h193b9818gd62dg67b7gf4e0g1d6b13d33a89" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Thunder)</content>
  <content contentuid="h86990efage02cg7a58gc14dgac02e5274f97" version="1">Level 5: Wild Resurgence</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6ef2813g5893gbc58ga19aga900b5ff9a74" version="1">You can restore one use of Wild Shape by expending a spell slot (no action required).</content>
  <content contentuid="h4fc2af8fg81c5g79b5g40c7gfd252be60f4c" version="1">Wild Resurgence</content>
  <content contentuid="h70ae88b1gd34eg0e8ag5b7bga526ea0cf7a6" version="1">You can restore one use of Wild Shape by expending a spell slot (no action required).</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d0f6247g32e9g935cg8e24g277269d5eee0" version="1">Circle of the Moon Spells</content>
  <content contentuid="h97d1904cg83d1gdb83ge2b8gfb2e45881c92" version="1">You can cast Circle of the Moon Spells while you’re in Wild Shape.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81a318d3g7d25ge9f7g6cb8g0d641f9d7d75" version="1">Fount of Moonlight</content>
  <content contentuid="h7133dd62g2ff3g5631g286cgfb7c7edec60f" version="1">Until the spell ends, you have Resistance to Radiant damage, and your melee attacks deal an extra [1] on a hit.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a281f4cgfc20gce12g5a55ge741d085a992" version="1">Fount of Moonlight</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0a594f4gbcafg3438g8e4cg19d60ca756cd" version="1">Until the spell ends, you have Resistance to Radiant damage, and your melee attacks deal an extra [1] on a hit.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9501eaeg3c65g8261gbbbegc5a79478ce47" version="1">Fount of Moonlight</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d3aa54bg7cf4g12d5g0d79g21d13c55e1c1" version="1">Level 6: Improved Circle Forms</content>
  <content contentuid="h25a52b4bg965bga6bdgaee9gb81edcb888e9" version="1">While in a Wild Shape form, you can add your Wisdom modifier to your Constitution saving throws.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f91f61fg551cg9fe6g9a0cg340e7bc48a41" version="1">Level 10: Moonlight Step</content>
  <content contentuid="h4b611e19g3e33g0533g1f8cg44ab465667b3" version="1">You magically transport yourself, reappearing amid a burst of moonlight. As a Bonus Action, you teleport up to [1] to an unoccupied space you can see. You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9203385fgb0d0gc75egca31g0264dad5cc14" version="1">Moonlight Step</content>
  <content contentuid="hde80ec9cg7cdbg9ea0g9225gb25148c847a9" version="1">You magically transport yourself, reappearing amid a burst of moonlight.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcf67e29ag6032g30cfgf7dbg0fb20210f91d" version="1">Moonlight Step Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd5cf1b2gd583gccb7gb15cg0cd8f525eccb" version="1">The number of times you can use your Moonlight Step.</content>
  <content contentuid="h019511d5gb330g2cd9gd860g84e25789d117" version="1">A constellation of a wise dragon appears on you. When you make a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; to maintain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Concentration"&gt;Concentration&lt;/LSTag&gt; on a spell, a roll result of 9 or lower is considered a 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="h539b326cga713g3705gbe13g1aa9f8c71bde" version="1">Level 2: Tactical Mind</content>
  <content contentuid="h61388cf8g2c44ge32ege2c8gd43ed94d46c8" version="1">You have a mind for tactics on and off the battlefield. You can expend a use of your Second Wind to push yourself toward success. You roll 1d10 and add the number rolled to the ability check, potentially turning it into a success.</content>
  <content contentuid="h25de2a50g4c8dg2b55gea44gd2074336ba6a" version="1">Second Wind Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ef6a3c5gfadagaff9gd6e8gf62d1e802c10" version="1">The number of times you can use your Second Wind or Tactical Mind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h33994fb3gfae3gde33g720fg2e4b5fa64c9d" version="1">Level 5: Tactical Shift</content>
  <content contentuid="h34197e5dgf2d4g066fgdb45gb041adb38595" version="1">Whenever you activate your Second Wind with a Bonus Action, you can move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h32fafe3dg30eeg2c3agc543g698e6d46c741" version="1">Tactical Shift</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd6115a2g072eg747bg10e1gc93f7616eafe" version="1">Whenever you activate your Second Wind with a Bonus Action, you can move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h62511cd9g27d2g5cbcga820gbb50c459d998" version="1">Level 9: Indomitable</content>
  <content contentuid="hb015b8bcg9783ge81ag0118gaa1388097f11" version="2">If you fail a saving throw, you can instead treat it as a success. Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h852a89d3g128fga1e5g2fedg98ddac129936" version="1">If you fail a saving throw, you can instead treat it as a success. </content>
  <content contentuid="h858b33e5g3b62g9b7fg692fg50cb883ac903" version="1">Tactical Master: Push</content>
  <content contentuid="h69435982g810ege56dgacebg3bb3b371ccd9" version="1">You can additionally apply the Push mastery property to that attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6c90bdcbg9d73g2f85g8df7g47fbedfb078f" version="1">Level 9: Tactical Master</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c920020g431dge64eg8e26g01537cb63450" version="1">When you make a weapon attack, you can additionally apply one of the Push, Sap, or Slow mastery properties to that attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h53c4a6c9g7930g55a2ga6d9g74f864e922d2" version="1">Tactical Master: Sap</content>
  <content contentuid="h0558e9e5gd74bg0f9fg2820gc589e678173e" version="1">You can additionally apply the Sap mastery property to that attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bcf613agff33gdd61g8288g83128f467505" version="1">Tactical Master: Slow</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd56201dg7690g59deg5771g7c00df6810c1" version="1">You can additionally apply the Slow mastery property to that attack.</content>
</contentList>