<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="h6b384962g5a7bg33e2g8993g0708cacc7834" version="3">Rule: Equipping Weapons</content>
  <content contentuid="h7e686044g6737gd055gea94g27a7a4c34341" version="3">You can equip weapons when you make an attack as part of attack action. Equipping a weapon includes drawing it from a sheath or picking it up.</content>
  <content contentuid="haf418bd4gaf68g349dge3fbg4db2a9970409" version="1">Dodge</content>
  <content contentuid="h40481577g00cege926g9b8cg4479348271b0" version="1">Until the start of your next turn, any attack roll made against you has Disadvantage, and you make Dexterity saving throws with Advantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h77f164a8g908ag78fdg969cg13b085d02634" version="2">If you reach 0 hit points, you fall Unconscious and must make Death Saving Throws. On 3 successes, you stop bleeding out and become Stable. On 3 failures, you die. If you roll a 20 on the d20, you regain 1 Hit Point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you regain any hit points, the condition is removed. If an ally &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Help"&gt;Helps&lt;/LSTag&gt; you, you regain 1 hit point.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd91b86adge685g5c21gf879g457242b186f2" version="2">While you have the Prone condition, you experience the following effects:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restricted Movement: You must spend an amount of movement equal to half your Speed to stand up and end the condition. If your Speed is 0, you can’t stand up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attacks Affected: An attack roll against you has Advantage if the attacker is within [1] of you. Otherwise, that attack roll has Disadvantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d9f934eg7721gfb63gcff8gb411e659dc78" version="1">Rule: One Spell with a Spell Slot per Turn</content>
  <content contentuid="hd3ffb028g9755g52adgf223g4bb289eebf93" version="1">On a turn, you can expend only one spell slot to cast a spell. This rule means you can’t, for example, cast a spell with a spell slot using the Magic action and another one using a Bonus Action on the same turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb60d9b3bg491bg7056g1bd9gc752b67bfd56" version="1">Mastery Properties: Cleave</content>
  <content contentuid="h57100728g823cg76f4g4795g878063b680ae" version="2">If you hit a creature with a melee attack roll using this weapon, you can make a melee attack roll with the weapon against a second creature within [1] of the first that is also within your reach. On a hit, the second creature takes the weapon’s damage, but don’t add your ability modifier to that damage unless that modifier is negative. You can make this extra attack only once per turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h240aa2f4g6571ge23eg8142g83ee7b985b8d" version="1">Mastery Properties: Graze</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fbee9aag6abeg6294g3fd8gbeb26ffd19f6" version="1">If your attack roll with this weapon misses a creature, you can deal damage to that creature equal to the ability modifier you used to make the attack roll. This damage is the same type dealt by the weapon, and the damage can be increased only by increasing the ability modifier.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbe460a9gf800gdb75g15bbg2b81a80fe8ab" version="1">Mastery Properties: Nick</content>
  <content contentuid="h84f8977cg06ecg1e31gebd6g21e4b7346121" version="1">When you make an attack with your off-hand weapon, you can make one additional attack as part of that attack. You can make this additional attack only once per turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h64e7021cg8b69g3f60gde38gd59f3cdc5846" version="1">Mastery Properties: Push</content>
  <content contentuid="h694f6a66g0531g98f0ga23eg525e146eb4d7" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon, you can push the creature up to [1] straight away from yourself if it is Large or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="haf74199bg92cbg93dega0fbgebb535603f83" version="1">Mastery Properties: Sap</content>
  <content contentuid="h6846e460g6aecg1e76g52c0g8c751abe8744" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon, that creature has Disadvantage on its next attack roll before the start of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb839de91gb995ge42eg62b9g1dd41fe4da4b" version="1">Mastery Properties: Slow</content>
  <content contentuid="h7773a857g54d9g0e61gc338g5671eef1378d" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon and deal damage to it, you can reduce its Speed by [1] until the start of your next turn. If the creature is hit more than once by weapons that have this property, the Speed reduction doesn’t exceed [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="ha395ebeag3995g70fage1d7g718229b74f9b" version="1">Mastery Properties: Topple</content>
  <content contentuid="h5af643b9gd1b7g259cg51cegf17292ec2f43" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon, you can force the creature to make a Constitution saving throw (DC 8 plus the ability modifier used to make the attack roll and your Proficiency Bonus). On a failed save, the creature has the Prone condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdfca5f76g305cgff0cg0532gbc6b23ff9367" version="1">Mastery Properties: Vex</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0019ff2g27f5g13abg7a86g646b2f8a1f55" version="1">If you hit a creature with this weapon and deal damage to the creature, you have Advantage on your next attack roll against that creature before the end of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a51e8b8gf631gf9b1g55bdg6af9de9235ef" version="1">Greataxe, Halberd</content>
  <content contentuid="hfdefde84gd74bg13d6g3599g34e7bc9cbafe" version="1">Glaive, Greatsword</content>
  <content contentuid="h0de5940ag21a0gff32gb8dfg01c84e54f73e" version="1">Dagger, Light Hammer, Sickle, Scimitar</content>
  <content contentuid="h6fd4a879g6dd9g5936gc329gc012af72f9c6" version="1">Greatclub, Pike, Warhammer, Heavy Crossbow</content>
  <content contentuid="h05a1ab8cg6b39gabd2g55c7g3a1f851c31fb" version="1">Mace, Spear, Flail, Longsword, Morningstar, War Pick</content>
  <content contentuid="h53e29765gaf78g1680g5805g24b5594244ac" version="1">Club, Javelin, Light Crossbow, Sling, Longbow, Musket</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ab19fdega28dg1fd1g0de1gc672bac4e6d3" version="2">Quarterstaff, Battleaxe, Maul, Trident</content>
  <content contentuid="hd724f72fgcda8gb6acgb5c4gd95d169dd0b4" version="1">Handaxe, Shortbow, Rapier, Shortsword, Hand Crossbow, Pistol</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e0a316bg6ce3gc18fgb7c0ge96c73d6dfa0" version="1">Weapon Mastery</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c28362ag369agee34gc8d4g6ccec5460b53" version="1">Your training with weapons allows you to use weapon mastery properties.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you reach certain levels in your class, you gain the ability to use the mastery properties of additional weapon types.</content>
  <content contentuid="he54ffab7g9288g792age85bg3fc0a39a63db" version="1">Level 1: Rage</content>
  <content contentuid="ha33a602cg9bb2gec42g889dg5983a5346c84" version="1">You can imbue yourself with a primal power called Rage, a force that grants you extraordinary might and resilience. You can enter it as a Bonus Action if you aren’t wearing Heavy armor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can enter your Rage the number of times shown for your Barbarian level in the Rages column of the Barbarian Features table. You regain one expended use when you finish a Short Rest, and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8abec533g47afgabaag5370ga724a70ed863" version="1">Level 1: Unarmoured Defence</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc1b8fd5g336eg3648g3224g9cae0aaac491" version="1">Level 2: Danger Sense</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6dea583g9359gddf3g2360g74669f67b1a6" version="1">Level 3: Primal Knowledge</content>
  <content contentuid="h860b399bg558cg749fgb64bg707d53758400" version="2">You gain proficiency in another skill of your choice from the skill list available to Barbarians at level 1.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, while your Rage is active, you can channel primal power when you attempt certain tasks; whenever you make an ability check using one of the following skills, you can make it as a Strength check even if it normally uses a different ability: Acrobatics, Intimidation, Perception, Stealth, or Survival. When you use this ability, your Strength represents primal power coursing through you, honing your agility, bearing, and senses.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3fa58ccfg135bg7a66g14degc3c8b5bb8261" version="1">Level 5: Fast Movement</content>
  <content contentuid="h7c047839g4177g2aaega022g36a5cb07886a" version="1">Level 7: Feral Instinct</content>
  <content contentuid="h28d4b453gc36cg810egf9e2g1dbff5d018d8" version="1">Level 7: Instinctive Pounce</content>
  <content contentuid="hdb025275gf26dg03dfg7370g4dddf3f0ffb9" version="1">As part of the Bonus Action you take to enter your Rage, you can move up to half your Speed.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6144726g336aga60cg63d6gf6c4bc669e6a" version="1">Level 9: Brutal Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a320da8g90b9g9714ge237g45c9782afbd0" version="1">If you use Reckless Attack, the target takes an extra 1d10 damage of the same type dealt by the weapon or Unarmed Strike, and you can cause one Brutal Strike effect of your choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forceful Blow. The target is pushed [1] straight away from you. You can then move up to half your Speed straight toward the target without provoking Opportunity Attacks.&lt;br&gt;Hamstring Blow. The target’s Speed is reduced by [1] until the start of your next turn. A target can be affected by only one Hamstring Blow at a time—the most recent one.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf41a9d96ge143g36f0g9f1eg51d9ca5a4cee" version="1">Reckless Attack: Forceful Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="hab5f59ebgf7a8g70bag4453g8c9195f80563" version="1">The target is pushed [1] straight away from you. You can then move up to half your Speed straight toward the target without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebd8f833g052cg4774g5e19geb34be606a5f" version="1">Reckless Attack: Hamstring Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="h0eff4b2bgeb61g4e62ga1ffg3b4f777317e1" version="1">The target’s Speed is reduced by [1] until the start of your next turn. A target can be affected by only one Hamstring Blow at a time—the most recent one.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2fea2840g0902gdf2bg7797g549c20c3d6e3" version="1">Forceful Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd10eb1fgc367ga39egd371g5e071e079549" version="1">You can move up to half your Speed straight toward the target without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5311cf0g6f4fg9a03g45f9gf5ba41e2994c" version="1">Hamstring Blow</content>
  <content contentuid="hcba666bcgdd43g5b9agef09gdcfd2c3d20ff" version="1">The Speed is reduced by [1] until the start of attacker's next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebad3866ga362g915cge97fg661e8b92ea36" version="1">Level 11: Relentless Rage</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd45d1c1g9dd3g206agfb7eg456c6af02ac0" version="1">Once per &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ShortRest"&gt;Short Rest&lt;/LSTag&gt;, when you would drop to [1] &lt;LSTag Tooltip="HitPoints"&gt;hit points&lt;/LSTag&gt; while &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="RAGE"&gt;Enraged&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you instead regain hit points equal to twice your Barbarian level and avoid being &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="DOWNED"&gt;Downed&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h784061e1gf2a8g748bg99cfg9e391dd4569c" version="1">Level 3: Frenzy</content>
  <content contentuid="hd21b5d53gc033g82abgfcdag21730bb83c68" version="1">If you use Reckless Attack while your Rage is active, you deal extra damage to the first target you hit on your turn with a Strength-based attack. To determine the extra damage, roll a number of d6s equal to your Rage Damage bonus, and add them together. The damage has the same type as the weapon or Unarmed Strike used for the attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f8570c9g2cd6g2327g3c99g18d5c393bf5e" version="1">Level 6: Mindless Rage</content>
  <content contentuid="h42189866g05d1g89b4g6e9dg1f97d248b2a9" version="1">Level 10: Retaliation</content>
  <content contentuid="hde644cc1g1dc6g103bg095ege867e6fa22ad" version="1">When you take damage from a creature that is within [1] of you, you can take a Reaction to make one melee attack against that creature, using a weapon or an Unarmed Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc8de1446g6777ge942g7572g5cd9d6cc8f14" version="1">Boot of the Giants</content>
  <content contentuid="hf411e734g4162g32ddg2c68g075dce673ed3" version="1">Try to kick a target away. Your chances depend on your Athletics, and are higher if you're hidden or invisible.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5acf268bg7a2dgd7c7g4d2dg20caffe2e8a4" version="1">You can kick targets up to twice the weight that &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Shove"&gt;Shoving&lt;/LSTag&gt; them would allow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e7ef600g82aegeba0g077eg2ddad69731f8" version="1">Surrounded by a barbarian's wild magic. Your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; increases by an amount equal to your Rage Damage bonus until your &lt;LSTag Type="Status" Tooltip="RAGE"&gt;Rage&lt;/LSTag&gt; ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd75d1783g8062gae55g78a6g651f55455f7f" version="1">Level 2: Jack of All Trades</content>
  <content contentuid="h6002075bg4feegb25ag03b5g8e88a4351c0f" version="1">Level 5: Font of Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="h5d1b01ffgd776g8ca4gd2edgb4e5e0068ad7" version="1">In addition, you can expend a spell slot (no action required) to regain one expended use of Bardic Inspiration.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3c4853cag177dg4ea8g0c15gde7e940ee735" version="1">Font of Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="h7c14769cg0f8ag7968g4156g1272fd5b7850" version="3">Expend a spell slot to regain one expended use of Bardic Inspiration.</content>
  <content contentuid="he36b3403gbab9gf77fg17fbg32e95953478c" version="1">Level 7: Countercharm</content>
  <content contentuid="h1dedae79g3922gbd27g0925g98aec4318fa7" version="1">You can use musical notes or words of power to disrupt mind-influencing effects. If you or a creature within 30 feet of you fails a saving throw against an effect that applies the Charmed or Frightened condition, you can take a Reaction to cause the save to be rerolled, and the new roll has Advantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf8844bacg4eb3geecdg5fbagf17d5ba9d6b0" version="1">Countercharm</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f358bf7g4a10gc77fg43cfg0c187137ef7a" version="1">You can use musical notes or words of power to disrupt mind-influencing effects. If you or a creature within 30 feet of you fails a saving throw against an effect that applies the Charmed or Frightened condition, you can take a Reaction to cause the save to be rerolled, and the new roll has Advantage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3169b2acg5134gbc8dge8fagb01eabf3a278" version="1">Level 3: Beguiling Magic</content>
  <content contentuid="h035b29c1g51d0ge9f8gb63fgc75cd5045b0c" version="2">You always have the Charm Person and Mirror Image spells prepared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, immediately after you cast an Enchantment or Illusion spell using a spell slot, you can cause a creature you can see within [1] of yourself to make a Wisdom saving throw against your spell save DC. On a failed save, the target has the Charmed or Frightened condition (your choice) for 1 minute</content>
  <content contentuid="he30a14f7gb323g888eg2ff5g04b0a7374497" version="1">Beguiling Magic: Charmed</content>
  <content contentuid="haac5a803g73dfg5282g175eg12c90e9a77cd" version="1">Beguiling Magic: Frightend</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e9e444agc6b5g3056g6b60g447875f0ec07" version="1">Level 3: Mantle of Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="hd68a192ag408cg0b94ge1bcgb6efd87c7b6a" version="2">You can weave fey magic into a song or dance to fill others with vigor. As a Bonus Action, you can expend one use of Bardic Inspiration and roll your Bardic Inspiration die. When you do so, choose a number of other creatures within [1] of yourself, up to your Charisma modifier (minimum of one creature).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h719facf1g5f1cg71c4gbf18g0bc0200d571d" version="2">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd927a3dfg462bg2162g0ddegc1f29c11bb86" version="1">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3f5c8f9g2b3bg1058g7715gee2645709a64" version="1">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h52a153aag53d8g2658g72aegc55c7baffc11" version="1">Each of those creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h530230d7ge34cg06b9g06a3ge16228b8a608" version="1">Creatures gains Temporary Hit Points equal to twice the number rolled on the Bardic Inspiration die, and each can move without provoking Opportunity Attacks until the end of its next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcc01542ag2ea8ge230g53b5g6bae54a352d2" version="1">Level 3: Cutting Words</content>
  <content contentuid="hfac955c9g640eg8dc8gfdefgfa559fa195f8" version="3">Extra Attack (Cantrip)</content>
  <content contentuid="he6112d47g8846ge668gbd97g45ddd36eeb46" version="1">You can attack twice instead of once whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, you can cast one of your cantrips that has a casting time of an action in place of one of those attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1a1b446eg2636gca22g7bafg910726511c02" version="1">Aid</content>
  <content contentuid="h5380e85fg27eagff54gaa61g803d6710929e" version="1">Choose up to three creatures within range. Each target’s Hit Point maximum and current Hit Points increase by [1] for the duration.</content>
  <content contentuid="he6319c8dga9bagd985gfc80gc057d99c3f06" version="1">Aid</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c0c79e8geefage313gb534gd315de67d298" version="1">Increase your allies' hit point maximum by [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="hbdf4d91ege560gf373gb78fgc694716131ec" version="1">Word of Radiance</content>
  <content contentuid="h0dd0eba8g9b93g7909g9d9cg2a09e01a4c46" version="2">Level 1: Divine Order: Protector</content>
  <content contentuid="h82c38cb3g39e6g13c8g7a26g5c63f737aa79" version="1">Protector: Trained for battle, you gain proficiency with Martial weapons and training with Heavy armor.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd91012edgb1a6g4aabg14d4g0d685464de55" version="1">Thaumaturge: You know one extra cantrip from the Cleric spell list. In addition, your mystical connection to the divine gives you a bonus to your Intelligence (Arcana or Religion) checks. The bonus equals your Wisdom modifier (minimum of +1).</content>
  <content contentuid="h5eae110bgf170g8febg7b95gaf9957eab275" version="1">Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="hf42e4215gdaa7g8b2cg6d6cg34b3a7233576" version="1">Light</content>
  <content contentuid="h08e84982gdf0fgadf1g29d5g02cc8281827c" version="2">Bursting Sinew</content>
  <content contentuid="hf2980afegb1f3g08e3g5b30g296c1e8141b7" version="1">Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h3dc64960ga68egb106gddd9g8a83f2e5394a" version="1">Sacred Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="h37124d24g1b0dg1b86g632dg14623f5d21b6" version="1">Spare the Dying</content>
  <content contentuid="h31c6269fga1bfge0a9gb4bfg7f845b81b38a" version="1">Thaumaturgy</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d2d81f9g6a4cg493ege377gd246536aefa0" version="1">Toll the Dead</content>
  <content contentuid="h5d663b96gee20gd7abg28bdgde325d686903" version="1">Divine Order</content>
  <content contentuid="hf078c843g4ca9gd89bgde69g7b94c3d7e9b4" version="1">You have dedicated yourself to one of the following sacred roles of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc0f7da49g83b0g2364gd22fg0e72e6d0f671" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Word of Radiance</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d5b8b7cg1eddg15a0g6e0cgb4e68f50ee06" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="h865f785bge303g1b8ag2f0egee91191a55fd" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Light</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bfe486dga99eg5aefg818agacd35ff6e130" version="2">Level 1: Divine Order: Bursting Sinew</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5ac78c8g2d8cg02bag6ebbg2f9ccd67bc36" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h63c03147gca42g60bdgfa7ag47ceb695bc38" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Sacred Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="hf2f5e5c4g141ag2b8egb90cg9ff6727b6910" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Spare the Dying</content>
  <content contentuid="h50136471gff21g505fg888cgf856fc01281a" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Thaumaturgy</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b0eeaeeg6a13gc99dg6669gc97c57ec0db5" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Toll the Dead</content>
  <content contentuid="h84a7d362gf65ag0f66g6103g7d1f4fc707d2" version="1">Level 2: Channel Divinity</content>
  <content contentuid="h619804afg28a4g6f48g9db2gb39ec7c1d073" version="1">You can channel divine energy to create special effects such as Divine Spark and Turn Undead, choosing one each time you use Channel Divinity. Additional effects and uses are gained at higher Cleric levels. You regain one use on a Short Rest and all uses on a Long Rest. Saving throw DCs use your Spellcasting DC.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fdb1f5ag867fg21d4g6beeg681eae4df812" version="1">Divine Spark</content>
  <content contentuid="he5c89bffgb42ege4daga349g64ec3fecb28f" version="1">As a Magic action, you point your Holy Symbol at another creature you can see within [1] of yourself and focus divine energy at it. You either restore Hit Points to the creature or force the creature to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, the creature takes Necrotic or Radiant damage (your choice). On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage (round down).</content>
  <content contentuid="h49ee25b5g5f2age7acga266g96075d1e4240" version="1">Divine Spark: Heal</content>
  <content contentuid="hbcd0c295g2003g99d5ge6fcg5fad76be07bb" version="1">You restore Hit Points to a creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b82bf91ge1b7g4b75g2472g3c3dbf201a2d" version="1">Divine Spark: Radiant Damage</content>
  <content contentuid="hb95127abg79cag5782ge868geb1002d62c1c" version="1">You deal damage to a creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9db3b3abg7a4dg3f7fg42a9g43591b76887d" version="1">Divine Spark: Necrotic Damage</content>
  <content contentuid="hb1119630g31c7g738eg4a76g56eb77fe86bc" version="1">Level 7: Blessed Strikes: Divine Strike (Radiant)</content>
  <content contentuid="hb14ca27eg593ag392fgab27g2186f2a37316" version="2">Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with an attack roll using a weapon, you can cause the target to take an extra [1]</content>
  <content contentuid="ha5f17982g16bdg018bg655eg1db1622f5096" version="1">Level 7: Blessed Strikes: Divine Strike (Necrotic)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd61761e0gbebfg6542gac8bgd70ab3faa548" version="1">Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with an attack roll using a weapon, you can cause the target to take an extra 1d8 Necrotic.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbdc1e3fg886agebc7gf898gdd7b5aea06a3" version="1">Level 7: Blessed Strikes: Potent Spellcasting</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d199d0egf3a1ga886gf931gb46f01ab73e5" version="1">Potent Spellcasting. Add your Wisdom modifier to the damage you deal with any Cleric cantrip.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4bebd04fg3a81gc270gd50bga237aecd8ef8" version="1">Blessed Strikes</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c4d3581gf44cg6a9ag27f8ge9f2dd54d6ed" version="1">Divine power infuses you in battle. You gain one of the following options of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6ac0f1cg84d4g5137g1a23g92f5941f06dc" version="1">Level 5: Sear Undead</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9e8561fg5920g7f26g9d66g15b2d44e24f3" version="1">Spare the Dying</content>
  <content contentuid="hb742b3aagabfcg536cg10e0g99bbe354e49a" version="1">Heal a creature within range that has 0 Hit Points and isn’t dead.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd085b0deg3cc9g0858gdf14geef98a4164c3" version="1">Word of Radiance</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb7ccd06g2737gdcf2gc167g21f32c9615fb" version="1">Burning radiance erupts from you in a [1] Emanation. Each creature of your choice that you can see in it must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf652a768gef39g78fdg661dg8ddbb887d3f3" version="1">Level 3: Disciple of Life</content>
  <content contentuid="h748a060egc16cg7d82gf97eg22830dd0c9f1" version="1">When a spell you cast with a spell slot restores Hit Points to a creature, that creature regains additional Hit Points on the turn you cast the spell. The additional Hit Points equal 2 plus the spell slot’s level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h45db170cgfec9gad8eg1591gd99ec7aa2b2c" version="1">Level 6: Blessed Healer</content>
  <content contentuid="h6f58f448gfe00g1b2agab56g46c8bf14ca5f" version="1">The healing spells you cast on others heal you as well. Immediately after you cast a spell with a spell slot that restores Hit Points to one or more creatures other than yourself, you regain Hit Points equal to 2 plus the spell slot’s level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae1dce65g444ag6a6egf7d3g354c47c64531" version="1">Preserve Life</content>
  <content contentuid="hf73a03f1g9a62g7708g6ac9ge3ea9b45c4a8" version="1">As a Magic action, you present your Holy Symbol and expend a use of your Channel Divinity to evoke healing energy that can restore a number of Hit Points equal to five times your Cleric level. Choose Bloodied creatures within [1] of yourself (which can include you), and divide those Hit Points among them.</content>
  <content contentuid="haed19d90g7118gfa81g42d5gba4d717eba4c" version="1">Blooded</content>
  <content contentuid="h28bdf1edg1a62gc8a2gc601gdedb4f01f3b6" version="1">This creature’s Hit Points have dropped below 50%.</content>
  <content contentuid="h12e63398gc863ged08g09d8g9e2fffc91af3" version="1">Channel Divinity</content>
  <content contentuid="h62870381g3b8dgbb2cgfc78gf6ba26bd778f" version="1">The number of times you can channel your divine powers.</content>
  <content contentuid="h39b48f39g9a41g2ba3g3567g7ab1cb265f82" version="1">Level 3: Warding Flare</content>
  <content contentuid="ha7d55e66g6f97ga4b7g45b4g5829f0c36910" version="2">When a creature that you can see within [1] of yourself makes an attack roll, you can take a Reaction to impose Disadvantage on the attack roll, causing light to flare before it hits or misses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h67f1e6b2g8adcge989g555ag3cbae9d62375" version="1">Level 6: Improved Warding Flare</content>
  <content contentuid="hcac62cb2g678dgbdc4g4a80g875b53ed7a48" version="1">You regain all expended uses of your Warding Flare when you finish a Short or Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, whenever you use Warding Flare, you can give the target of the triggering attack a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to 2d6 plus your Wisdom modifier.</content>
  <content contentuid="h772e3772g49fdg8cf4g0f02g893153584b30" version="1">Warding Flare</content>
  <content contentuid="h6c1ab5a0g8a40g1755g2eacg01f53db2903f" version="1">When a creature that you can see within 30 feet of yourself makes an attack roll, you can take a Reaction to impose Disadvantage on the attack roll, causing light to flare before it hits or misses.</content>
  <content contentuid="h03dc1992g1d8agc3e0ga6bbg22607e81d966" version="1">Warding Flare (Ally)</content>
  <content contentuid="hcb0f1d4dg6ea8gf1eag5e72g32b56f306af2" version="1">Warding Flare (Self)</content>
  <content contentuid="hdc4e30afg0702g20ddgf4a5g1751c8b46770" version="1">Level 3: Invoke Duplicity</content>
  <content contentuid="h31748432g34ebg740cgf353g2071d6cae486" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you can expend one use of your Channel Divinity to create a perfect visual illusion of yourself in an unoccupied space you can see within [1]. The illusion lasts for 1 minute. As a Bonus Action, you can move the illusion up to [1] to another unoccupied space you can see.</content>
  <content contentuid="h002b7ed0g2d07g9ecbg0301g13b767a04c7e" version="1">Level 6: Trickster’s Transposition</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d5766b9g0e51g3888g5633gd570f3096a0f" version="1">Whenever you take the Bonus Action to create or move the illusion of your Invoke Duplicity, you can teleport, swapping places with the illusion.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha73b8276g56b2g1bdegc73bgf16610d268ab" version="1">Trickster’s Transposition</content>
  <content contentuid="h82f58797g491fg0f3ag42b4g05c22ee9679d" version="1">Whenever you take the Bonus Action to create or move the illusion of your Invoke Duplicity, you can teleport, swapping places with the illusion.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5220d58g095fg5ae1g7115g72d15a96ef0c" version="1">You can supernaturally inspire others through words, music, or dance. This inspiration is represented by your Bardic Inspiration die, which is a d6.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using Bardic Inspiration. As a Bonus Action, you can inspire another creature within 60 feet of yourself who can see or hear you. That creature gains one of your Bardic Inspiration dice. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once within the next hour when the creature fails a D20 Test, the creature can roll the Bardic Inspiration die and add the number rolled to the d20, potentially turning the failure into a success. A Bardic Inspiration die is expended when it’s rolled.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number of Uses. You can confer a Bardic Inspiration die a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Higher Levels. Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain Bard levels, as shown in the Bardic Die column of the Bard Features table. The die becomes a d8 at level 5, a d10 at level 10, and a d12 at level 15.</content>
  <content contentuid="h63129871gfb37gc314g1fdfg9b10303bcc26" version="1">Level 1: Bardic Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="h2810e8cag53f2gddb2gb1bbg7d5f6848ec0b" version="1">You can supernaturally inspire others through words, music, or dance. This inspiration is represented by your Bardic Inspiration die, which is a d6.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using Bardic Inspiration. As a Bonus Action, you can inspire another creature within 60 feet of yourself who can see or hear you. That creature gains one of your Bardic Inspiration dice. A creature can have only one Bardic Inspiration die at a time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once within the next hour when the creature fails a D20 Test, the creature can roll the Bardic Inspiration die and add the number rolled to the d20, potentially turning the failure into a success. A Bardic Inspiration die is expended when it’s rolled.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Number of Uses. You can confer a Bardic Inspiration die a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Higher Levels. Your Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach certain Bard levels, as shown in the Bardic Die column of the Bard Features table. The die becomes a d8 at level 5, a d10 at level 10, and a d12 at level 15.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e25c63eg08ebg12a0gfefega65d73c0d540" version="1">Level 3: War Priest</content>
  <content contentuid="h04fd168age75cg9dadgeb9bgce0ceddefc4c" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you can make one attack with a weapon or an Unarmed Strike. You can use this Bonus Action a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once). You regain all expended uses when you finish a Short or Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3c0eb0ffga3ccgcf65g862bg01f7c36b74b8" version="1">War Priest</content>
  <content contentuid="h8686f980g14cdg48cdg0923g21540c804c00" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you can make one attack with a weapon or an Unarmed Strike.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ea2f219gec23g1a96ga5efgce5d1bc88951" version="1">War Priest Extra Attack Charge(s)</content>
  <content contentuid="ha96c97feg6fd1gc562g799fgde13a4800459" version="1">Point used to gain an extra attack as a bonus action.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4dc018cagbaa3ga624g7da2g0a6dab9353ce" version="1">Level 3: Guided Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="ha052e514g0261g1570g0745g00d44f89cc3d" version="1">When you or a creature within 30 feet of you misses with an attack roll, you can expend one use of your Channel Divinity and give that roll a +10 bonus, potentially causing it to hit. When you use this feature to benefit another creature’s attack roll, you must take a Reaction to do so.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81ab1ec4g5097gf34cg7f12g4d040607771b" version="1">Guided Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h900f0f0bgcd61g0708g6d02gf89738f718de" version="1">Level 6: War God’s Blessing</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c6d3ec2g7683g7e9fg7d62g08a6874b3c5f" version="1">You can expend a use of your Channel Divinity to cast Shield of Faith or Spiritual Weapon rather than expending a spell slot. When you cast either spell in this way, the spell doesn’t require Concentration. Instead the spell lasts for 1 minute, but it ends early if you cast that spell again, have the Incapacitated condition, or die.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3bb1c07ag3913g5b74g9454gdcebc7737556" version="1">Shield of Faith: War God’s Blessing</content>
  <content contentuid="hcaeae1ebgf2c5gb598g6716gb1b7c699916c" version="1">Spiritual Weapon: War God’s Blessing</content>
  <content contentuid="h002f5e57g1181g2dbbg226fgf29f606b801c" version="1">Steel Wind Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h0da58492g230cg424fg00cdg006fb672dd4d" version="1">You flourish the weapon used in the casting and then vanish to strike like the wind. Choose up to five creatures you can see within range. Make a melee spell attack against each target. On a hit, a target takes [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="h84a10acdg5e1fgb4f6g3b55g7f5134f52d10" version="1">Mind Spike</content>
  <content contentuid="h05f1c3ebg02fcg677cga473g464cac2d584f" version="1">You drive a spike of psionic energy into the mind of one creature you can see within range. The target makes a Wisdom saving throw, taking Psychic damage on a failed save or half as much damage on a successful one. On a failed save, you also always know the target’s location until the spell ends. While you have this knowledge, the target can’t become hidden from you, and if it has the Invisible condition, it gains no benefit from that condition against you.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd666f94dg1a88g5b93g7dcbgfbc951360305" version="1">Synaptic Static</content>
  <content contentuid="haddaa3c4ga780gc6c0g5533g2da826d6931f" version="1">You cause psychic energy to erupt at a point within range. Each creature in a  [1] radius Sphere centered on that point makes an Intelligence saving throw, taking Psychic damage on a failed save or half as much damage on a successful one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a failed save, a target also has muddled thoughts for 1 minute. During that time, it subtracts 1d6 from all its attack rolls and ability checks, as well as any Constitution saving throws to maintain Concentration. The target makes an Intelligence saving throw at the end of each of its turns, ending the effect on itself on a success.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc29da1ffgb5d5g29c2g97c3g2050946f5a23" version="1">Mind Spike</content>
  <content contentuid="h3aac9e83g2f2ag85ddgcf84ge7224ea85b8b" version="1">The creature’s location is always known to the spellcaster until the spell ends. The creature can’t hide from the spellcaster, and if it has the Invisible condition, it gains no benefit from that condition against the spellcaster.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0eb6a1ccg061cg7757g2ce7gb1ae17ae8a0f" version="1">Synaptic Static</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e56e88cg0481g2c87g52e7g140df577385c" version="1">The creature subtracts 1d6 from all its attack rolls and ability checks, as well as from any Constitution saving throws it makes to maintain Concentration. At the end of each of its turns, the target makes an Intelligence saving throw, ending the effect on a success.</content>
  <content contentuid="h32658116g9dc9g1364g0f58g311a9cad82b8" version="1">Level 3: Mind Magic</content>
  <content contentuid="h2035dcdeg7b97g47a9gcfb1gb7bc1f9c6cb9" version="2">As a Magic action, you can expend one use of your Channel Divinity to manifest your magical knowledge. Choose one spell from the Knowledge Domain or the Divination school. As part of the same action, you cast the chosen spell without expending a spell slot.</content>
  <content contentuid="h75bd2293g6a4eg35b3g4781gf184d224ea59" version="1">Level 6: Unfettered Mind</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd98d6aage020gf00bgcd6fg4be2ad2fd956" version="1">You gain proficiency in Intelligence saving throws.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Add half of your Wisdom Modifier to &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityCheck"&gt;Ability Checks&lt;/LSTag&gt; that you are not &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Proficiency"&gt;Proficient&lt;/LSTag&gt; in.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf5d6de51g8683g514bgcfd2gd52016de99fe" version="1">Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="h9cbc738dgd21bg77f4g2687gd1ac412ca2b4" version="1">You launch a mote of light at one creature or object within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes Radiant damage, and until the end of your next turn, it emits Dim Light in a [1] radius and can’t benefit from the Invisible condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d4e8665g6567g3bc4gd9f1g206db8efad20" version="1">Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="he44a89e4gd251g9a1dg6abagca1e9807a226" version="1">The creature emits Dim Light in a [1] radius and can’t benefit from the Invisible condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d4a4bb1g65b7g5025g4514gdfa80f1282ba" version="1">Thunderclap</content>
  <content contentuid="h853f3b07gf693g964eg9f97g97a2cfda50ef" version="1">Each creature in a [1] Emanation originating from you must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or take Thunder damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd2e3aa0g3258g4710g9504gbadee9cd0ea6" version="1">Level 1: Druidic</content>
  <content contentuid="h59f8cb26gc1aag4dc3g0939ge1b311504647" version="1">You know Druidic, the secret language of Druids. While learning this ancient tongue, you also unlocked the magic of communicating with animals; you always have the Speak with Animals spell prepared.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1193aa13ge0d7ge702g2f85ga0c0527d229d" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Warden</content>
  <content contentuid="h236eb2e6g63d1g6008gac03gd13912a2af7b" version="1">Warden. Trained for battle, you gain proficiency with Martial weapons and training with Medium armor.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdc66e2feg6dc9g8e0dg69c3g1ac135e77240" version="1">Level 1: Primal Order: Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="h261201bdgf3e1gc0a9g001bg9f21c4b6eb0b" version="1">Magician. You know one extra cantrip from the Druid spell list. In addition, your mystical connection to nature gives you a bonus to your Intelligence (Arcana or Nature) checks. The bonus equals your Wisdom modifier (minimum bonus of +1).</content>
  <content contentuid="hf498864agc7beg3cdbgca11g269c576f1a01" version="1">Guidance</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e0c0b74gabceg8644g0a67g8c877d23dd83" version="1">Level 1: Primal Order: Poison Spray</content>
  <content contentuid="h3635dadfgfe4eg55c4g39dfgaf968256d2d8" version="1">Poison Spray</content>
  <content contentuid="h5307ff13g4736g2ce2ga66fg11f20a990de2" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Produce Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="h5169409cg04adgc907gd30eg09ebe8d3738c" version="1">Produce Flame</content>
  <content contentuid="h55c47b09ga380g8cf2g15b8g2bedd46fe8e9" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="h69ae862bga7a4g2605g04a4gd9317e169763" version="1">Resistance</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0c364a3g050eg598bgd2fdg4c1b525be149" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Shillelagh</content>
  <content contentuid="h599263a1g8987g0f3dgf199g149b6068247f" version="1">Shillelagh</content>
  <content contentuid="hab8ea7d9g7419g79d4ge012g86380a295a02" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: SpareTheDying</content>
  <content contentuid="hf5a7c07dg5d75g8b41g3ce4g8e350dae85b9" version="1">SpareTheDying</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5bb58c8g9203g4533gc615ga31bea2a2187" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="h8891553bg7ca5g791ag4b95g5a72f6e71ed4" version="1">Starry Wisp</content>
  <content contentuid="hc7a0905fg5836g8050gb036gd435c6a53ffd" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Thorn Whip</content>
  <content contentuid="h1793f9fbgf70agf3acge48bg70b646b51326" version="1">Thorn Whip</content>
  <content contentuid="h566f5dd1g1db3g0d0age62cg0ff1909892ef" version="1">Level 1: Divine Order: Thunderclap</content>
  <content contentuid="hf81ea6f0gb2bcg2e34g72c5gfeb99fd56826" version="1">Thunderclap</content>
  <content contentuid="ha16fbd5eg7072g66aeg7f0eg739d38d2a607" version="1">Primal Order</content>
  <content contentuid="h22f70fd0g4354g1c46g6712gdc288b7803e5" version="1">You have dedicated yourself to one of the following sacred roles of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb670c3bdg0b18g5834g24e2gce9406adf925" version="1">Wild Shape Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e2c2a49gb8a7g78d8gf687gb0cdc6987be7" version="1">The number of times you can use your Wild Shape.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f1b692bg604cgb34cg9e64g7c5d22aebe85" version="1">Level 2: Wild Shape</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6dea6aag9290gf3cegeb8ag0351bd8d0fc5" version="2">You can use a Bonus Action to transform into a known Beast form using Wild Shape. You can end the transformation early as a Bonus Action. You can use Wild Shape twice. You regain one expended use when you finish a Short Rest, and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest. When you assume a Wild Shape form, you gain a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to your Druid level. You can’t cast spells, but shape-shifting doesn’t break your Concentration or otherwise interfere with a spell you’ve already cast.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1505dff7gb11cg17eageb5dg29f041ed571a" version="1">Level 2: Wild Shape</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e8ebc40g6f5cg5d29gc885g2f7fb0f2899b" version="1">Wild Shape</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e1bf345gb5fcg3bbag17c4g7ac514e8455e" version="1">When you assume a Wild Shape form, you gain a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to your Druid level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8a519044g61f3g7166g3e0cg6c97799602e4" version="1">Wild Shape: Badger</content>
  <content contentuid="h9c56ac47g3984g90a8g0115g3a3000abd94a" version="1">Wild Shape: Polar Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h55c8bb9fgab04g0e14gce66g6d7734c64973" version="1">Wild Shape: Cat</content>
  <content contentuid="h4bd8abf4gf0adgc66cgc5bag97c641b5e998" version="1">Wild Shape: Deep Rothé</content>
  <content contentuid="hb0d5b816gde08g18fag0b3dg87d87c0c5144" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Raven</content>
  <content contentuid="h5290eb7agca74g04fdg1c90gf56091132a96" version="1">Wild Shape: Giant Spider</content>
  <content contentuid="h78df260fgc265gf45fg5e7eg3a5e3f320112" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d5751c2gc7e1ge1c7g2187gc1dfba8f54e2" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="hfad853e7g6d71gc847gc4e1g6c0f425eab30" version="1">Wild Shape: Badger</content>
  <content contentuid="h94425109g11ccg2387g6f3ag6e092535cfc7" version="1">Wild Shape: Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h125b5a75g4894g085age46age0c6df5c916e" version="1">Wild Shape: Black Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="hc5ea7296g02acg34fdgfa7ag6fdba9447454" version="1">Wild Shape: Grey Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h57fcc347g64cfgce00g9684gdc1711bf0132" version="1">Wild Shape: Polar Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="hb16c19a4gbaaege05bg81b8g91dc2a6ce3ba" version="1">Wild Shape: Boar</content>
  <content contentuid="h5ea20feag7ba3g2debga31dg2a7068efca9a" version="1">Wild Shape: Deep Rothé</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a2047d4g2ebbg73b4gae60g085e395a05a1" version="1">Wild Shape: Spider</content>
  <content contentuid="h43604180gb8bag2721g1fb6g15bf4761d06f" version="1">Wild Shape: Rat</content>
  <content contentuid="h2478c66ag72fbg9200g36ecga9a3f81bd052" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Raven</content>
  <content contentuid="head73bd1g04bfg7aedgaa38g5e91178238da" version="1">Wild Shape: Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h356d9ca7gde59g20cdg3b43g5d69b5e91166" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9efa391g3349g9633gd775ge547b21394a6" version="1">Wild Shape: Sabre-Toothed Tiger</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4e0bdf5g2bedgdb25gd9c5ge125ee988248" version="1">Wild Shape: Panther</content>
  <content contentuid="h4a06421fg399bge851g94a3gc50cf5ac4685" version="1">Wild Shape: Dilophosaurus</content>
  <content contentuid="h98a60dc7g4df3g01fbg8fd5g832b47cc24aa" version="1">Wild Shape: Owlbear</content>
  <content contentuid="h4171bc8fg8509g75b1g344ag4875cb305165" version="1">Wild Shape: Air Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd2efd2eag8f2ag8c20g6458g2d2ee404e737" version="1">Wild Shape: Earth Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="ha20f8cafgc437g2e56ga015ge90f46a9fa2e" version="1">Wild Shape: Fire Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1247016g50d4g5313gc5d9g817268c918e1" version="1">Wild Shape: Water Myrmidon</content>
  <content contentuid="hdcc80e1bg50d8g4d7egf3c5gd88613415b9a" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fbca55age4a4g5797ga82fge26fc359b66c" version="1">Wild Shape: Wolf</content>
  <content contentuid="h4838ee09g3746g4dc0g2baeg7a9ddd9bf1d4" version="1">Wild Shape: Dire Raven</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a5396efg111ag7d25gf58fgce2d27775b14" version="1">Wild Shape: Rat</content>
  <content contentuid="h82d61545g3d50gbd71gb81cg49ba5440aca5" version="1">Wild Shape: Spider</content>
  <content contentuid="he834ae45gcae8gf3bag6df2ga3f6b92b7407" version="1">Wild Shape: Deep Rothé</content>
  <content contentuid="h434d69begc8f3gbd6cg78e1gc7b1896221ee" version="1">Wild Shape: Boar</content>
  <content contentuid="h5cdd815bge132g3d37gdabfg758fee1fd2ff" version="1">Wild Shape: Polar Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h267295feg37f1gf983g6cedg02a6401df1fd" version="1">Wild Shape: Grey Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="hd15c9166gcb1dg4177g3646gbdb76e9200cc" version="1">Wild Shape: Black Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d42344bg665dge300g935bg0d9887bee468" version="1">Wild Shape: Bear</content>
  <content contentuid="h59a5a380g59f1gfdb0g9a4fgef72e80eb679" version="1">Wild Shape: Badger</content>
  <content contentuid="h556b4fb3g5a97gb81cg3f21gd57ac1f02a0d" version="1">%%% EMPTY</content>
  <content contentuid="h978ef6fag7931g203cg08ccge7b0c344b3e8" version="1">Level 3: Circle Forms</content>
  <content contentuid="h69bf3828g083cg1e10g408egf0f2ee4c7fe8" version="1">You can channel lunar magic when you assume a Wild Shape form, granting you the benefits below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armor Class: Until you leave the form, your AC equals 13 plus your Wisdom modifier if that total is higher than the Beast’s AC.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Temporary Hit Points: You gain a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to three times your Druid level.</content>
  <content contentuid="h50a84c2agc47eg3409gfbf3g8b9efe860b49" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Potent Spellcasting</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbacd095g40f6g7468g5750g2f164c7506d4" version="1">Potent Spellcasting. Add your Wisdom modifier to the damage you deal with any Druid cantrip.</content>
  <content contentuid="h623803a7gceadgfb71gf1d2g9f3e3921f3f2" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Cold)</content>
  <content contentuid="h1cfad235g00bdg10bfgf085g60ac289d2534" version="1">Primal Strike. Once on each of your turns when you hit a creature with an attack roll using a weapon or a Beast form’s attack in Wild Shape, you can cause the target to take an extra [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="he3035afbgf846g4686gf4e6gc39575739bed" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Fire)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0a6f226g6b60g6204gb543g086832d392ff" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Lightning)</content>
  <content contentuid="h193b9818gd62dg67b7gf4e0g1d6b13d33a89" version="1">Level 7: Elemental Fury: Primal Strike (Thunder)</content>
  <content contentuid="h86990efage02cg7a58gc14dgac02e5274f97" version="1">Level 5: Wild Resurgence</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6ef2813g5893gbc58ga19aga900b5ff9a74" version="1">You can restore one use of Wild Shape by expending a spell slot (no action required).</content>
  <content contentuid="h4fc2af8fg81c5g79b5g40c7gfd252be60f4c" version="1">Wild Resurgence</content>
  <content contentuid="h70ae88b1gd34eg0e8ag5b7bga526ea0cf7a6" version="1">You can restore one use of Wild Shape by expending a spell slot (no action required).</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d0f6247g32e9g935cg8e24g277269d5eee0" version="1">Circle of the Moon Spells</content>
  <content contentuid="h97d1904cg83d1gdb83ge2b8gfb2e45881c92" version="1">You can cast Circle of the Moon Spells while you’re in Wild Shape.</content>
  <content contentuid="h81a318d3g7d25ge9f7g6cb8g0d641f9d7d75" version="1">Fount of Moonlight</content>
  <content contentuid="h7133dd62g2ff3g5631g286cgfb7c7edec60f" version="1">Until the spell ends, you have Resistance to Radiant damage, and your melee attacks deal an extra [1] on a hit.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7a281f4cgfc20gce12g5a55ge741d085a992" version="1">Fount of Moonlight</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0a594f4gbcafg3438g8e4cg19d60ca756cd" version="1">Until the spell ends, you have Resistance to Radiant damage, and your melee attacks deal an extra [1] on a hit.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9501eaeg3c65g8261gbbbegc5a79478ce47" version="1">Fount of Moonlight</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d3aa54bg7cf4g12d5g0d79g21d13c55e1c1" version="1">Level 6: Improved Circle Forms</content>
  <content contentuid="h25a52b4bg965bga6bdgaee9gb81edcb888e9" version="1">While in a Wild Shape form, you can add your Wisdom modifier to your Constitution saving throws.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f91f61fg551cg9fe6g9a0cg340e7bc48a41" version="1">Level 10: Moonlight Step</content>
  <content contentuid="h4b611e19g3e33g0533g1f8cg44ab465667b3" version="1">You magically transport yourself, reappearing amid a burst of moonlight. As a Bonus Action, you teleport up to [1] to an unoccupied space you can see. You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9203385fgb0d0gc75egca31g0264dad5cc14" version="1">Moonlight Step</content>
  <content contentuid="hde80ec9cg7cdbg9ea0g9225gb25148c847a9" version="1">You magically transport yourself, reappearing amid a burst of moonlight.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcf67e29ag6032g30cfgf7dbg0fb20210f91d" version="1">Moonlight Step Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd5cf1b2gd583gccb7gb15cg0cd8f525eccb" version="1">The number of times you can use your Moonlight Step.</content>
  <content contentuid="h019511d5gb330g2cd9gd860g84e25789d117" version="1">A constellation of a wise dragon appears on you. When you make a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt; to maintain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Concentration"&gt;Concentration&lt;/LSTag&gt; on a spell, a roll result of 9 or lower is considered a 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="h539b326cga713g3705gbe13g1aa9f8c71bde" version="1">Level 2: Tactical Mind</content>
  <content contentuid="h61388cf8g2c44ge32ege2c8gd43ed94d46c8" version="1">You have a mind for tactics on and off the battlefield. You can expend a use of your Second Wind to push yourself toward success. You roll 1d10 and add the number rolled to the ability check, potentially turning it into a success.</content>
  <content contentuid="h25de2a50g4c8dg2b55gea44gd2074336ba6a" version="1">Second Wind Charge</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ef6a3c5gfadagaff9gd6e8gf62d1e802c10" version="1">The number of times you can use your Second Wind or Tactical Mind.</content>
  <content contentuid="h33994fb3gfae3gde33g720fg2e4b5fa64c9d" version="1">Level 5: Tactical Shift</content>
  <content contentuid="h34197e5dgf2d4g066fgdb45gb041adb38595" version="1">Whenever you activate your Second Wind with a Bonus Action, you can move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h32fafe3dg30eeg2c3agc543g698e6d46c741" version="1">Tactical Shift</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd6115a2g072eg747bg10e1gc93f7616eafe" version="1">Whenever you activate your Second Wind with a Bonus Action, you can move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h62511cd9g27d2g5cbcga820gbb50c459d998" version="1">Level 9: Indomitable</content>
  <content contentuid="hb015b8bcg9783ge81ag0118gaa1388097f11" version="2">If you fail a saving throw, you can instead treat it as a success. Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h852a89d3g128fga1e5g2fedg98ddac129936" version="1">If you fail a saving throw, you can instead treat it as a success. </content>
  <content contentuid="h858b33e5g3b62g9b7fg692fg50cb883ac903" version="1">Tactical Master: Push</content>
  <content contentuid="h69435982g810ege56dgacebg3bb3b371ccd9" version="1">You can additionally apply the Push mastery property to that attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6c90bdcbg9d73g2f85g8df7g47fbedfb078f" version="1">Level 9: Tactical Master</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c920020g431dge64eg8e26g01537cb63450" version="1">When you make a weapon attack, you can additionally apply one of the Push, Sap, or Slow mastery properties to that attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h53c4a6c9g7930g55a2ga6d9g74f864e922d2" version="1">Tactical Master: Sap</content>
  <content contentuid="h0558e9e5gd74bg0f9fg2820gc589e678173e" version="1">You can additionally apply the Sap mastery property to that attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bcf613agff33gdd61g8288g83128f467505" version="1">Tactical Master: Slow</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd56201dg7690g59deg5771g7c00df6810c1" version="1">You can additionally apply the Slow mastery property to that attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1261d64eg6ff9gfcfcg691agbb4378c7bc02" version="2">Rule: Strength Requirement (Chain Mail)</content>
  <content contentuid="he349bc27ga203ge868g3f0ag5fdf65b7e83b" version="1">If a creature wearing this Heavy Armor has a Strength score lower than [1], its Speed is reduced by [2].</content>
  <content contentuid="h412ee86dgfedcga2beg54adgbd1f6bc466f9" version="1">Rule: Strength Requirement (Splint Armor)</content>
  <content contentuid="h1855925eg36d7g774cg4917gc8135001356f" version="1">Rule: Strength Requirement (Plate Armor)</content>
  <content contentuid="h36e05e75gb0acgebbeg511ag25cc56fcde31" version="1">If a creature wearing this Heavy Armor has a Strength score lower than [1], its Speed is reduced by [2].</content>
  <content contentuid="h1378b9e1g8e8cgbb1eg3cb7g5aad15a2e9d3" version="1">Level 3: Remarkable Athlete</content>
  <content contentuid="h8a4c8a20gcc89g49e5g2025g934de8342619" version="1">Thanks to your athleticism, you have Advantage on Initiative rolls and Strength (Athletics) checks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, immediately after you score a Critical Hit, you can move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h070ecbffg0669ge021gd9f2gf9d31bf77f88" version="1">Remarkable Athlete</content>
  <content contentuid="h20fe10e3g6a5cg1394g9602g64f7640b6f6d" version="1">Immediately after you score a Critical Hit, you can move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdc98f803g35c5gf1e3g8979g2a5e77165301" version="1">Level 10: Heroic Warrior</content>
  <content contentuid="ha8f342f0g6dafg2cb0g07ffg5de2b08f710e" version="1">The thrill of battle drives you toward victory. During combat, you can give yourself Heroic Inspiration whenever you start your turn without it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6ae0967eg345cg0ef5g653cg5c51675a3b5a" version="1">Heroic Warrior: Reroll Attacker's Die</content>
  <content contentuid="h7e67754bg739bg3c96gcd25g72c30f60a4d8" version="1">Force a creature to reroll its &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt;. </content>
  <content contentuid="h81c64052g4f2bg8257g3f1ag716712683b25" version="1">Heroic Warrior: Reroll with Advantage</content>
  <content contentuid="h4dfef820g9b72g3d0egde23ga602945eec3c" version="1">Gain &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Roll&lt;/LSTag&gt; or &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throw&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h40d89fa7ga96bgd2a5g9917g93f8ac20286b" version="1">Heroic Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="h82e9547dg2a57g3068g6744g22536b77a26f" version="1">Level 10: Eldritch Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h4f0291dage2acga1e7g22a4ga4748a927a0d" version="1">Extra Attack 2 (Cantrip)</content>
  <content contentuid="h9a6cdeb9g51d2g4ed0gb4e4gb453d3f8c2e7" version="1">You can attack three times instead of once whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, you can cast one of your cantrips that has a casting time of an action in place of one of those attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="hea3538f1g6d4fgd692gdf5cg16c0c6d70258" version="1">Extra Attack 2 (Cantrip)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd383ab64gcd01g6437g4439gcce1bcafb30c" version="1">You can attack three times instead of once whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, you can cast one of your cantrips that has a casting time of an action in place of one of those attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h66ceeddfg85e7gf6e6g45fdgf681167aa694" version="1">Level 10: Improved Combat Superiority</content>
  <content contentuid="h1a9ea1d9gcca2gd533gd087g0e05473a8b97" version="1">Level 1: Unarmored Defense</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6df1fdbgd732gf839g1534g7c3a49d1d89d" version="1">While you aren’t wearing armor or wielding a Shield, your base Armor Class equals 10 plus your Dexterity and Wisdom modifiers.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9693b20eg4b48g52f3g8ec0gd315398b9984" version="1">Level 1: Martial Arts: Dextrous Attacks</content>
  <content contentuid="h24c5605eg0a01ge915g6899g61b6123a76ea" version="1">You gain the following benefits while you are unarmed or wielding only Monk weapons and you aren’t wearing armor or wielding a Shield.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bdd8181g1932g81d9g02c5g5f889a86df8f" version="1">Level 1: Martial Arts: Martial Arts Die</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e235ae9geb66g5d58g1353gd372c6850cab" version="1">You gain the following benefits while you are unarmed or wielding only Monk weapons and you aren’t wearing armor or wielding a Shield.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6bd2af0gd6f7g18c7g118fgea0d3d7cc5c5" version="1">Level 1: Martial Arts: Bonus Unarmed Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="he192df4agfe10gd5ceg7151gebb776ff39e4" version="1">You can make an Unarmed Strike as a Bonus Action.</content>
  <content contentuid="h98c8bddbge30fgeb55gb667gd793986d0ded" version="1">You gain the following benefits while you are unarmed or wielding only Monk weapons and you aren’t wearing armor or wielding a Shield.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1fc430dg69bagc256g2318g1055bfa2fc27" version="1">Patient Defense</content>
  <content contentuid="h4c44c0abg262cg8e6egf06cg92cf676855e3" version="1">You can expend 1 Focus Point to take both the Disengage and the Dodge actions as a Bonus Action.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd4e66dbg0ac9g5c5dg463eg6076392563ce" version="1">Step of the Wind</content>
  <content contentuid="h83374bedgf40agd759g1784gd9c5f24545a3" version="1">You can expend 1 Focus Point to take both the Disengage and Dash actions as a Bonus Action, and your jump distance is doubled for the turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h554e1c9cgf636g08a4gf6ebg1d3611ee623a" version="1">Step of the Wind</content>
  <content contentuid="ha6d44a5ag5a9ag0c67gfbb0ge9a5772193c3" version="1">Your jump distance is doubled for the turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e2c71efgf381g9eb7gaf5cg2760015a45e2" version="1">Dash</content>
  <content contentuid="hdfc28510gf4cdgb66eg531fg3918cc8b3df9" version="1">Cover more distance this turn: double your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h78c4f622gbb2cg3636gb74cg733fbf8d0b37" version="1">Disengage</content>
  <content contentuid="h5248daffg03b1g4eeeg4498gaafc4796eece" version="1">Retreat safely: moving won't provoke &lt;LSTag Tooltip="OpportunityAttack"&gt;Opportunity Attacks&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h62169240g157dg0599gc2d2g3c5611236273" version="1">Level 2: Unarmored Movement</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd7cc0dcg93b5g2722g9ad5g75eb1fd5edf9" version="1">Level 6: Unarmoured Movement</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb2da776g993fg5373g95abg3f33446175c5" version="1">Level 10: Unarmoured Movement</content>
  <content contentuid="hfe07c960gd6d9ga0e1g4facgbbfc0b0a2079" version="1">Level 2: Uncanny Metabolism</content>
  <content contentuid="hfaa042d3gf744gb60fg226bgaec318afadb8" version="1">You can regain all expended Focus Points. When you do so, roll your Martial Arts die, and regain a number of Hit Points equal to your Monk level plus the number rolled.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d5fdddcg3d1bg2ed8g0bebgcfcf2293742c" version="1">Uncanny Metabolism</content>
  <content contentuid="h48a9451fg4097gddefg1177g77b625d48f82" version="1">You can regain all expended Focus Points. When you do so, roll your Martial Arts die, and regain a number of Hit Points equal to your Monk level plus the number rolled.</content>
  <content contentuid="h399b9569g4416g07fbg0cd6ga4f008d8e40c" version="1">Level 3: Deflect Attacks</content>
  <content contentuid="h363f8861g503bg174cgc576g28e60841fa32" version="3">When an attack hits you and deals bludgeoning, piercing, or slashing damage, you can take a Reaction to reduce the total damage you take. The reduction equals 1d10 + your Dexterity modifier + your monk level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this reduces the damage to 0, you can spend 1 Ki Point to use Redirect Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h45c562c6gf2cag3a18gb7a8g96ddfe88db60" version="1">Deflect Attacks</content>
  <content contentuid="h2abe271ag6c58g52b7g96c5ge33fc7fc4c92" version="1">Deflect Attacks: Redirect</content>
  <content contentuid="h96997b05g813bg4cedge308g8b97a39ea6cc" version="1">Reduce the bludgeoning, piercing, or slashing damage you take by 1d10 + your Dexterity &lt;LSTag Tooltip="AbilityModifier"&gt;modifier&lt;/LSTag&gt; + your monk level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If this reduces the damage to 0, you can spend 1 Ki Point to use Redirect Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f7f1f15gc38bgcaeeg96aegf18e8377c301" version="1">Reduce the damage and redirect it back at your attacker.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd8199896gbae1g11ceg6ba1g523b41f8b9ef" version="1">Deflect Attack: Redirect</content>
  <content contentuid="h4487767egdb77g3708g93a8gd0279452056a" version="1">Reduce the damage and redirect it back at your attacker.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha8c51db9g127cg0f8dgf557g402626436b8c" version="1">Level 4: Slow Fall</content>
  <content contentuid="h726e4c54g614fg70ccg5ebag4c572b51fbe4" version="1">Level 6: Empowered Strikes</content>
  <content contentuid="h3eabcb35gf264g4f8ag9c30g123cbc8fd2b8" version="2">Your unarmed strikes overcome &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Resistant"&gt;Resistance&lt;/LSTag&gt; to both nonmagical and magical damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6a55712gd62cgd5e7g68d8g0007496a3e1e" version="2">Level 9: Acrobatic Movement</content>
  <content contentuid="hcb9a361cg3dadgecb2gdae1g23fc5f5c3919" version="1">Level 7: Evasion</content>
  <content contentuid="h33c22a3cg9bbaga9c8g65e2g0701352832a0" version="1">Level 10: Heightened Focus</content>
  <content contentuid="h3bb523e2gc26eg22c2g87e9g4e1e0da5e1af" version="2">Your Flurry of Blows, Patient Defense, and Step of the Wind gain the following benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flurry of Blows: You can expend 1 Focus Point to use Flurry of Blows, making three Unarmed Strikes instead of two.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Patient Defense and Step of the Wind: When you expend a Focus Point to use either feature, you gain Temporary Hit Points equal to two rolls of your Martial Arts die.</content>
  <content contentuid="hddf40c2dge503g0c52g70e0g81df540da740" version="1">Heightened Focus</content>
  <content contentuid="h96955479gc03cg5656g398ega8e7e632c8a3" version="1">You gain a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to two rolls of your Martial Arts die.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb0d0ae76g515agec5dg8b3fgfef5c6b386f3" version="1">Level 10: Self-Restoration</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6524b85g7c46g835fg5ec8g505bf3a2d396" version="1">Level 10: Purity of Body</content>
  <content contentuid="hc41f1b91gbedcg876fg1542g2c46f2f4be27" version="1">Level 3: Shadow Arts</content>
  <content contentuid="h62e16743gcb72g9068gb2d0gb1a62ea9d321" version="1">You have learned to draw on the power of the Shadowfell, gaining the following benefits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Darkness. You can expend 1 Focus Point to cast the Darkness spell without spell components. You can see within the spell’s area when you cast it with this feature. While the spell persists, you can move its area of Darkness to a space within [1] of yourself at the start of each of your turns.&lt;br&gt;Darkvision. You gain Darkvision with a range of [1]. If you already have Darkvision, its range increases by 60 feet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shadowy Figments. You know the Minor Illusion spell. Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf18cec4dgc5a5gd248gadb2gacd0002e8ee0" version="1">Elemental Attunement</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd54bf99g06bfg8a6cg5904g1e14b2426411" version="2">At the start of your turn, you can expend 1 Focus Point to imbue yourself with elemental energy. The energy lasts for 10 minutes. You gain the following benefits while this feature is active.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reach: When you make an Unarmed Strike, your reach is [1] greater than normal, as elemental energy extends from you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Elemental Strikes: Whenever you hit with your Unarmed Strike, you can cause it to deal your choice of Acid, Cold, Fire, Lightning, or Thunder damage rather than its normal damage type. When you deal one of these types with it, you can also force the target to make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you can move the target up to [1] toward or away from you, as elemental energy swirls around it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h103f93c5g91eeg4b52g3977gd60b8e4ef8da" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Acid</content>
  <content contentuid="h1778d7a2g0b0cga6a0gcfcdg8f6f656d1e50" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Cold</content>
  <content contentuid="h5644171bg3f2cg52f1gc8dcgc1e6b38d6a9b" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Fire</content>
  <content contentuid="h60fd53fcgbe77gcb48gd29dg52f09c53ad87" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Lightning</content>
  <content contentuid="h459ce897gc32bgf940g855egc984bd313c7c" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Thunder</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c61ee4bg56f8gfe0fgb3c5g7712a4e3d87e" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Acid</content>
  <content contentuid="he11f6bc3ga347g550fg0466g52c1a9c5aad4" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Cold</content>
  <content contentuid="hb648df73g12d6gb0b3g24e3g1c88ad261547" version="1">Elemental Attunement: FIre</content>
  <content contentuid="habb49dadg47e5gc5bag6c56g45bf51c0e30c" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Lightning</content>
  <content contentuid="h33483b7agbd7cg35c6gf796g0a198715f127" version="1">Elemental Attunement: Thunder</content>
  <content contentuid="h1441fb09g0c66g1899g0bf1g7aee316c859c" version="1">Elemental Strikes: Pull</content>
  <content contentuid="h02454f9dg7610g957dg5d40g829bab542a09" version="1">Elemental Strikes: Push</content>
  <content contentuid="h05885430gd722g322ag7f6agbaf1e13b70fd" version="1">When you deal one of these types with it, you can also force the target to make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, you can move the target up to 10 feet toward or away from you, as elemental energy swirls around it.</content>
  <content contentuid="habf53306g66b3gb76ag5a1bgf0e155fe7d9b" version="1">Elemental Burst</content>
  <content contentuid="h637a148fgbbb7g2269gfdd1g3f81fddd5949" version="1">As a Magic action, you can expend 2 Focus Points to cause elemental energy to burst in a [1] radius Sphere centered on a point within [2] of yourself. Choose a damage type: Acid, Cold, Fire, Lightning, or Thunder.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each creature in the Sphere must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, a creature takes damage of the chosen type equal to three rolls of your Martial Arts die. On a successful save, a creature takes half as much damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h13e2605fg4015g36b3g1800g126360f78534" version="1">Elemental Burst: Acid</content>
  <content contentuid="heb32a441g2a41g2be1g94a8gfb7868573b40" version="1">Elemental Burst: Cold</content>
  <content contentuid="h20cb80c4gd3bag353egbaeagfc09e502126d" version="1">Elemental Burst: Fire</content>
  <content contentuid="hb75cfe1fg5fb8gb857g1067ge5e38e4b4046" version="1">Elemental Burst: Lightning</content>
  <content contentuid="ha9461978g325bg8b56g0b7fga747967bcf5b" version="1">Elemental Burst: Thunder</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0321dfag2f41g5984g2a27g4ba878286102" version="1">Level 11: Stride of the Elements</content>
  <content contentuid="h90c565bfgdc8eg1fc2gde60ga457cc60135b" version="1">While your Elemental Attunement is active, you also have a Fly Speed and a Swim Speed equal to your Speed.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbe92a07bg1800gd2e8g079fg1e0f39ce73ce" version="1">Wholeness of Body</content>
  <content contentuid="h4feabb8egaa22g3d36gc857g512930772995" version="1">Level 6: Wholeness of Body</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5f70284g45c5g71b8g7505g337ea5751295" version="1">You gain the ability to heal yourself. As a Bonus Action, you can roll your Martial Arts die. You regain a number of Hit Points equal to the number rolled plus your Wisdom modifier (minimum of 1 Hit Point regained).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h25c230c0g01dbg6406g2c50gfc3e4aa92e7f" version="1">Wholeness of Body</content>
  <content contentuid="h202adf83g5a60g677dg2f14g1cbdfc06aeab" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you can roll your Martial Arts die. You regain a number of Hit Points equal to the number rolled plus your Wisdom modifier (minimum of 1 Hit Point regained).</content>
  <content contentuid="hbbdecd13gacf6ga6bcge4dfga9e9fdd39678" version="1">Level 11: Fleet Step</content>
  <content contentuid="h9f4fd43dgb96cg804dg3440g15b0a150a3ec" version="1">You can use Step of the Wind without expending a Bonus Action.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e9a944dgb216gb539gf48dg822147b343bd" version="1">Rule: Strength Requirement (Heavy Melee Weapon)</content>
  <content contentuid="hd97fac61ge406g7715gc8b7g188472b4140a" version="1">If a creature wielding this Heavy weapon has a Strength score lower than [1], it has Disadvantage on attack rolls made with this weapon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h73497683g65cdged9eg85abge93a8ba9aede" version="1">Rule: Dexterity Requirement (Heavy Ranged Weapon)</content>
  <content contentuid="h07e8d8cdgee47gf8bdge26eg6ddb468803f3" version="1">If a creature wielding this Heavy weapon has a Dexterity score lower than [1], it has Disadvantage on attack rolls made with this weapon.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc453b2f8ga64fg8d50g0cb0g4a53f20b32d9" version="2">Level 3: Channel Oath</content>
  <content contentuid="ha840fbb3g435eg87ebgd676g3fc781ce7b67" version="1">You can channel oath energy directly from the Outer Planes, using it to fuel magical effects. You start with one such effect: Divine Sense, which is described below. Other Paladin features give additional Channel Oath effect options. Each time you use this class’s Channel Oath, you choose which effect from this class to create.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use this class’s Channel Oath twice. You regain one of its expended uses when you finish a Short Rest, and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest. You gain an additional use when you reach Paladin level 11.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a Channel Oath effect requires a saving throw, the DC equals the spell save DC from this class’s Spellcasting feature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h77c3bd23ge0bdg1ed9gc503g1a06cc920d08" version="1">Level 2: Paladin’s Smite</content>
  <content contentuid="hab240831g4170g3e19gaf78ge733be05a5f1" version="1">You always have the Divine Smite spell prepared. In addition, you can cast it without expending a spell slot, but you must finish a Long Rest before you can cast it in this way again.</content>
  <content contentuid="h39de8d3fgd862g0342g0a3ag9205f4e7bf55" version="1">Paladin’s Smite</content>
  <content contentuid="haaa7e52ege832ge271gecfdge010d65df535" version="1">You can cast Divine Smite without expending a spell slot, but you must finish a Long Rest before you can cast it in this way again.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd777f361gcaa7g7dbegeb0agb9179de1ba4b" version="1">Level 5: Faithful Steed</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d9bb995gd364g7b4fgd6f8gb78ed0bdda9b" version="1">You can call on the aid of an otherworldly steed. You always have the Find Steed spell prepared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can also cast the spell once without expending a spell slot, and you regain the ability to do so when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e887af9gf132g931bgf5ffgfd331943059d" version="1">Faithful Steed</content>
  <content contentuid="h0aaffea6g03a3g6185g2b3eg67a082d34700" version="1">You can also cast Find Steed once without expending a spell slot, and you regain the ability to do so when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h75d1a2deg8c23gb291g4a07g0b23ca7da55c" version="1">Find Steed</content>
  <content contentuid="hca271062g4f0eg4316gc46ag52e3d54b2851" version="3">You summon an otherworldly steed and immediately mount it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The steed can take one of the following actions of your choice on each of its turns: Dash, Disengage, Dodge, or Attack.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While mounted on the steed, when you take damage of 4 or higher, you must make a DC 8 Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, you fall off the steed and have the Prone condition for 1 turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only a player with a pure heart can see the steed.</content>
  <content contentuid="h969b831eg23d1g5115g756bg2f5d95f425ab" version="1">Find Steed</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e3d13a5gdd90g80a4g970dg3282a7a7bfa9" version="1">You summon an otherworldly steed and immediately mount it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The steed can take one of the following actions of your choice on each of its turns: Dash, Disengage, Dodge, or Attack.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While mounted on the steed, when you take damage of 4 or higher, you must make a DC 8 Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, you fall off the steed and have the Prone condition for 1 turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1a6f7528gc5efg5c9bge4f9gf7eb55315d54" version="1">Steed Action Point</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbb54662gd707gd172gbdfdgd57e57e3b819" version="1">The steed can take one of the following actions of your choice on each of its turns: Dash, Disengage, Dodge, or Attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="he8975525g4266g8430g813bg4d65176a35f5" version="1">Slam</content>
  <content contentuid="he8006ed5gf2f6gd6ceg798dg91c566666c82" version="1">Dodging</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c0401b6g3fc4gaadagf4bbg097715066c52" version="1">Focusing on avoiding attacks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;Br&gt;&lt;LSTag Tooltip="AttackRoll"&gt;Attack Rolls&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the affected entity have &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Disadvantage"&gt;Disadvantage&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and the entity has &lt;LSTag Tooltip="Advantage"&gt;Advantage&lt;/LSTag&gt; on Dexterity &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SavingThrow"&gt;Saving Throws&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3d4848abgc60eg631cgc713g605af144c9ee" version="1">Level 9: Abjure Foes</content>
  <content contentuid="h060adb3eg6617g9283g226fg6d070eb47c88" version="1">As a Magic action, you can expend one use of this class’s Channel Oath to overwhelm foes with awe. As you present your Holy Symbol or weapon, you can target a number of creatures equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum of one creature) that you can see within [1] of yourself. Each target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or have the Frightened condition for 1 minute.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha4ade769g56f1g989dg4a5dgc980f0453d08" version="1">Abjure Foes</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0938809g82f6ge8a7gea01gff762cf6f570" version="1">As a Magic action, you can expend one use of this class’s Channel Oath to overwhelm foes with awe. As you present your Holy Symbol or weapon, you can target a number of creatures equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum of one creature) that you can see within [1] of yourself. Each target must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or have the Frightened condition for 1 minute.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd546b3bg87ddg0b0eg91d9g7dd5bb69d0d5" version="1">Level 11: Radiant Strikes</content>
  <content contentuid="he923c53cgfecbgb456g1ee5gbc97fd5f5a9a" version="1">Your strikes now carry supernatural power. When you hit a target with an attack roll using a Melee weapon or an Unarmed Strike, the target takes an extra 1d8 Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1b6d335fg71e3g921bg96efgd3563a3e9d4b" version="1">The paladin and nearby allies have Resistance to Necrotic, Psychic, and Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="he4565ab2g2625gaeb8g694eg929ab02e448c" version="1">The paladin and nearby allies have Resistance to Necrotic, Psychic, and Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae6c4966g7a68ga1edg4bc6gae39ac7aeb6b" version="1">You and any nearby allies have Resistance to Necrotic, Psychic, and Radiant damage. The aura disappears if you fall Unconscious.</content>
  <content contentuid="h36197b70g60e1g9d30g020ag5ebf5202eade" version="1">Level 7: Relentless Avenger</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c05bd1dg9548g9d0ag66dbgd31ce3af6dab" version="1">If you hit an enemy with an &lt;LSTag Tooltip="OpportunityAttack"&gt;Opportunity Attack&lt;/LSTag&gt;, you can reduce the creature’s Speed to 0 until the end of the current turn. And your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; increases by [1] on your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd54cf49fg52f9gc82fg23ddg240455666d75" version="1">Relentless Avenger Foe</content>
  <content contentuid="h4580d441g9dc0gbc53g7a59g25cce7bd8ba2" version="1">Can't move. Restrained by an &lt;LSTag Tooltip="OpportunityAttack"&gt;Opportunity Attack&lt;/LSTag&gt; from a Relentless Avenger.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8a2bbcc7gff7eg7312gb3f5g2e15ba81d07c" version="1">Favored Enemy</content>
  <content contentuid="hcd8000b2gdb8aga27dg0c5agb3cd6b125346" version="1">You always have the Hunter’s Mark spell prepared. You can cast it twice without expending a spell slot, and you regain all expended uses of this ability when you finish a Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of times you can cast the spell without a spell slot increases when you reach certain Ranger levels, as shown in the Favored Enemy column of the Ranger Features table.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdfdce3a3g8fd1g0e71gf799gc4b6e93e4494" version="1">Level 1: Favored Enemy</content>
  <content contentuid="h306c6ef1gb334gc9d9g3199g2f6fed258ca6" version="1">You always have the Hunter’s Mark spell prepared. You can cast it twice without expending a spell slot, and you regain all expended uses of this ability when you finish a Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The number of times you can cast the spell without a spell slot increases when you reach certain Ranger levels, as shown in the Favored Enemy column of the Ranger Features table.</content>
  <content contentuid="h24da6064ga265g8748g66eeg77bdfbf8fe00" version="1">Level 6: Roving</content>
  <content contentuid="h7dcb940dged6eg6a11g5274gec876e4452ec" version="1">Your Speed increases by [1] while you aren’t wearing Heavy armor.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbe5c5e5fgade6g8f34g4b09g1cee59ffe473" version="1">Level 10: Tireless</content>
  <content contentuid="h60d6e7c1gc8cag3d1dgdaedg0d81cb025d8b" version="1">Primal forces now help fuel you on your journeys. As a Magic action, you can give yourself a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to 1d8 plus your Wisdom modifier (minimum of 1). You can use this action a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3229a845gf19dg1318g1141gf2138b76791c" version="1">Tireless</content>
  <content contentuid="h304ba6eegcc14g44c6g7640g0b3b0cf81a62" version="1">As a Magic action, you can give yourself a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to 1d8 plus your Wisdom modifier (minimum of 1). You can use this action a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h18c4df3eg4eabg12a1gbab7g044c7be445a5" version="1">Tireless</content>
  <content contentuid="hc95f4dcfg8caeg69e9gc8b5ge035fe1dc1a3" version="1">As a Magic action, you can give yourself a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to 1d8 plus your Wisdom modifier (minimum of 1).</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f7f0018g2af3g31ccg0cdbgcc4bb940f132" version="1">Tireless</content>
  <content contentuid="h3c5b5f7eg291agf227g9011gc0565f5cdd4d" version="1">As a Magic action, you can give yourself a number of Temporary Hit Points equal to 1d8 plus your Wisdom modifier (minimum of 1).</content>
  <content contentuid="hcff76038gf183g3e0cg380cgd7a4d9b485d4" version="1">Ranger</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd354410g485cg7eb3gce6cg2beae2ab9c6b" version="1">Rangers are unrivalled scouts and trackers, honing a deep connection with nature in order to hunt their favoured prey.</content>
  <content contentuid="h051d1aa3gfcbeg10d5g5326g1eec2d4e3962" version="1">Level 7: Exceptional Training</content>
  <content contentuid="he1cd6837ge579g13b4g4394g33ea8c725e00" version="1">Level 11: Bestial Fury</content>
  <content contentuid="h1fe98af2g42d0g348cga592g953cb60ce5e7" version="1">Level 5: Companion's Bond</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6c39153g0c9dg0ddeg1910g4688906cf811" version="1">Level 3: Dread Ambusher</content>
  <content contentuid="h761a2d1bgfaa4g6c2fgbda3g198675b6a886" version="1">You have mastered the art of creating fearsome ambushes, granting you the following benefits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ambusher’s Leap. At the start of your first turn of each combat, your Speed increases by [1] until the end of that turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dreadful Strike. When you attack a creature and hit it with a weapon, you can deal an extra [2]. You can use this benefit only once per turn, you can use it a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Initiative Bonus. When you roll Initiative, you can add your Wisdom modifier to the roll.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3b984b2eg48d2ga0a4g5cf8g78f1337ffab6" version="1">&lt;LSTag Tooltip="MovementSpeed"&gt;Movement speed&lt;/LSTag&gt; increased by [1].</content>
  <content contentuid="hbfb12c80g2d3cg0fc7ga570g61985f1e0903" version="1">Dreadful Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0903b4fgdab0g610fgf651g1cf01ed26e14" version="1">When you attack a creature and hit it with a weapon, you can deal an extra 2d6 Psychic damage. You can use this benefit only once per turn, you can use it a number of times equal to your Wisdom modifier (minimum of once), and you regain all expended uses when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5f7c0abdg7063gcfe9g177egb32caeb5c2c3" version="1">Dreadful Strike (Melee)</content>
  <content contentuid="hf3f8bd9cg3004g6dbbg08e2g587dc0432a14" version="1">Dreadful Strike (Ranged)</content>
  <content contentuid="h44cf5afdg1bddgc6d5g9577gcc6cc00bfd12" version="1">Level 7: Iron Mind</content>
  <content contentuid="h834d7e4cg19fdgd3acg2b88g50ab0030af80" version="1">You have honed your ability to resist mind-altering powers. You gain proficiency in Wisdom saving throws.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd3f07304gfb55ge28ega3f7g0cf1292516a3" version="1">Level 11: Stalker’s Flurry</content>
  <content contentuid="h374216bbgf985gc96cg64b3g959b101fd376" version="1">The Psychic damage of your Dreadful Strike becomes 2d8. The target must make a Wisdom saving throw against your spell save DC. On a failed save, a creature has the Frightened condition until the start of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are swift enough to turn a miss into a new strike. When you miss with a weapon attack, you can make another weapon attack for free.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd10997cg1b63g1960g4918ga9e47736c018" version="1">Level 11: Superior Hunter’s Prey</content>
  <content contentuid="h156a3a97g9e6bg053egabdeg9a8bfdfcdee2" version="1">Once per turn when you deal damage to a creature marked by your Hunter’s Mark, you can also deal that spell’s extra damage to a different creature that you can see within [1] of the first creature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2484eb83g2df9g26e8gd9a4g528b38f355d5" version="1">Superior Hunter’s Prey</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d51897ag955egeb37g57b9g59eddbb044d1" version="1">Steady Aim</content>
  <content contentuid="h8b43db08gaf12gc02agb86cge29d6c39df7f" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you give yourself Advantage on your next attack roll on the current turn. You can use this feature only if you haven’t moved during this turn, and after you use it, your Speed is 0 until the end of the current turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8cfd42a3ge9ddg2a7bg7928g2b06b4cc30ec" version="1">Steady Aim</content>
  <content contentuid="haf3b75e3g8f42g8af5ge959ga8ee656088f7" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you give yourself Advantage on your next attack roll on the current turn. You can use this feature only if you haven’t moved during this turn, and after you use it, your Speed is 0 until the end of the current turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4c5295e0g7006g010bg62b8gfa3c901f3027" version="1">Level 3: Steady Aim</content>
  <content contentuid="h49585eb0g7c75g3df5g4aacg38e6e664edb2" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you give yourself Advantage on your next attack roll on the current turn. You can use this feature only if you haven’t moved during this turn, and after you use it, your Speed is 0 until the end of the current turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdd434d50g0d94g6819ge916g55203c553e86" version="1">Level 7: Reliable Talent</content>
  <content contentuid="h21f511b2g92a9g1aafg61d4g9e8e4ad1e872" version="1">Level 5: Uncanny Dodge</content>
  <content contentuid="he94ba142g4f1bg9badge483g5c206c0854b1" version="1">Level 7: Evasion</content>
  <content contentuid="h97dd1bbcg1ca7g6953g67d7g155182b6526b" version="1">You can nimbly dodge out of the way of certain dangers. When you’re subjected to an effect that allows you to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, you instead take no damage if you succeed on the saving throw and only half damage if you fail. You can’t use this feature if you have the Incapacitated condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="h95ef44fegf44dg26b7g490bg4d2254baeba6" version="1">When you’re subjected to an effect that allows you to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, you instead take no damage if you succeed on the saving throw and only half damage if you fail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You don’t benefit from this feature if you have the Incapacitated condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0523c40bg9f42g36bcg9e1cg6081c59ba79a" version="1">Level 11: Improved Sneak Attack</content>
  <content contentuid="hd984038eg2324g666bg83degd9c1722e9df2" version="1">Your Sneak Attack’s damage dice increase by an additional 2d6.</content>
  <content contentuid="h29957e67gbc02g6407ga341g2f35096e19da" version="1">Level 9: Magical Ambush</content>
  <content contentuid="hfa85e2b2g9e54g0b5ag0128gfecef70e4d09" version="1">Level 3: Mage Hand Legerdemain</content>
  <content contentuid="hd3262b0cgdce0gf4d4g8fc6g529f4ebed5df" version="1">Level 3: Assassinate: Initiative</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4183fbcg8e1dg3584gff57g9ebed1bead51" version="2">You have Advantage on Initiative rolls.</content>
  <content contentuid="he1d36468gaf5dg2d18ge59agffc2c79d636d" version="1">Level 3: Assassinate: Surprising Strikes</content>
  <content contentuid="hf357f8d7g161dg5711g5d18gf26bc2d2273f" version="1">During the first round of each combat, you have Advantage on attack rolls against any creature that hasn’t taken a turn. If your Sneak Attack hits any target during that round, the target takes extra damage of the weapon’s type equal to your Rogue level.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc2fcccc7g38b5gff46g5362gc9de3dd4f7ea" version="1">Level 3: Assassin’s Tools</content>
  <content contentuid="h1164cde2g07a2g7ecag87dag7b7ebcb49bf2" version="1">You gain a Disguise Kit and a Poisoner’s Kit, and you have proficiency with them.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbd7ad3e9g7a42gc5e6gc2fdga2aedc0b75ce" version="2">Use Poisoner’s Kit: Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="h5a82f53dg51e2g741cg6a2dg0b0bcdccd4fd" version="1">Use Poisoner’s Kit: Toxin</content>
  <content contentuid="h39c54639gfc00g9983g819dg040b092116ce" version="1">Apply Toxin to your currently equipped weapon set.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c7b0986g2c44g4065gc905g112f0d2b3ba7" version="1">Apply Poison to your currently equipped weapon set.</content>
  <content contentuid="h23ed695dg9dc7gde96ge8bdgdd8f39573f79" version="1">The Poison you apply becomes more potent each time you reach Rogue levels 5 and 9.</content>
  <content contentuid="h38a88f4cg35f3g31d8g00d6g8d7544ea0cd0" version="1">Use Poisoner’s Kit</content>
  <content contentuid="h910e9fadg34c1gb42dg1da1g53563f066381" version="1">Apply Poison or Toxin to your currently equipped weapon set.</content>
  <content contentuid="h653acf2cg148dg50a8g434ag58a00ffde028" version="1">The Poison you apply becomes more potent each time you reach Rogue levels 5 and 9.</content>
  <content contentuid="heebd36b4ga479g75bcg0438gf61e56996e7a" version="1">Roving Aim</content>
  <content contentuid="hbdd3e730g8e9bgceceg9259g246346c857b2" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you give yourself Advantage on your next attack roll on the current turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6eedf8b2gca4cg0d52g60e6g6356346c4feb" version="1">Roving Aim</content>
  <content contentuid="hae41811bg62eeg0a5bge75bgde45ea1213a3" version="1">As a Bonus Action, you give yourself Advantage on your next attack roll on the current turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e517fa0g6790g8599ga038gec0254c7fae0" version="1">Level 9: Roving Aim</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ad37d2fg7e63g64e1g0db3g45844045ca7d" version="1">Your Speed isn’t reduced to 0 by using Steady Aim.</content>
  <content contentuid="he1072514g2359gf4c9g9ab0gf2fd8d2183ce" version="1">Level 3: Fast Hands</content>
  <content contentuid="h127592e2g23a4gc43cg2c3fgbbf222b3b2d1" version="1">You can use Throw as a Bonus Action.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3cad8c7eg48eeg5692g23c0g79706df73d92" version="1">Level 3: Second-Story Work</content>
  <content contentuid="h2fc3807bg34e4gbdbeg88f4gb50fa0facd7e" version="1">Throw: Fast Hand</content>
  <content contentuid="h60ea26b2gbcebg085dg4445g8f07a9d3ff4c" version="1">Paladin</content>
  <content contentuid="h3bda8161g54fbg0765gf90ag164a1cc634ba" version="1">A promise made so deeply that it becomes divine in itself flows through a paladin, burning bright enough to inspire allies and smite foes.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7cb6863bgbcc6g197agc84bg25e1ade48c39" version="1">Innate Sorcery</content>
  <content contentuid="he28b1437g3278g7202g8a7dg0bb7c36a5d7a" version="1">An event in your past left an indelible mark on you, infusing you with simmering magic. As a Bonus Action, you can unleash that magic for 1 minute, during which you gain the following benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spell save DC of your Sorcerer spells increases by 1.&lt;br&gt;You have Advantage on the attack rolls of Sorcerer spells you cast.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use this feature twice, and you regain all expended uses of it when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h59e594d8g8dd2ga3b4gd22fgc151ebfb31cd" version="1">Innate Sorcery</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c2324bag11d4g3d36g7a4eg5a90c1b041a2" version="1">An event in your past left an indelible mark on you, infusing you with simmering magic.</content>
  <content contentuid="h82f19e57gbf88g3a8bg03e7g5886ec5f6ac0" version="1">Innate Sorcery</content>
  <content contentuid="h591ca3fag8585g7042gec5dgab33a05594bb" version="1">An event in your past left an indelible mark on you, infusing you with simmering magic. As a Bonus Action, you can unleash that magic for 1 minute, during which you gain the following benefits:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The spell save DC of your Sorcerer spells increases by 1.&lt;br&gt;You have Advantage on the attack rolls of Sorcerer spells you cast.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can use this feature twice, and you regain all expended uses of it when you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf7441cebg5087gb813g35d8g6732e3fae8e6" version="1">Sorcery Point(s)</content>
  <content contentuid="h8b175862g0d58g482ag2d06g7b4654769d66" version="1">Sorcery Points are an important facet of a sorcerer's power. They can be spent to augment spells or access higher level &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slots&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9e4f723g5054g3b21ga6bage65df9a6ae78" version="1">Metamagic</content>
  <content contentuid="h98cf324dg4c24g1b78gdb54g670e46f0f8fb" version="1">You gain the ability to twist your spells to suit your needs. Choose from the following Metamagic options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You gain two more options at Sorcerer level 10.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha0496c74g4123g62d8ge5a6ga853a650ab6c" version="1">Sorcerous Restoration</content>
  <content contentuid="h5ef71f37g9eeeg0a14g2f05g417ed20720ed" version="1">You regain Sorcery Points equal to half your maximum.</content>
  <content contentuid="hea7a291eg87bag417cg8ac2gdece9fc65308" version="1">Level 7: Sorcery Incarnate</content>
  <content contentuid="hd8409099g42e6g3a17g9b47gc6bd4fec7de5" version="1">If you have no uses of Innate Sorcery left, you can use it if you spend 2 Sorcery Points when you take the Bonus Action to activate it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition, while your Innate Sorcery feature is active, your spell save DC increases by 2, rather than 1.</content>
  <content contentuid="h186d2005gce77g5134gd47dgcd1286eb95f5" version="1">Sorcerous Burst</content>
  <content contentuid="hf0be6fffg6e33g9c45g69bdg8f11958d0454" version="2">You cast sorcerous energy at one creature or object within range. Make a ranged spell attack against the target. On a hit, the target takes damage of a type you choose: Acid, Cold, Fire, Lightning, Poison, Psychic, or Thunder.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sometimes the magic surges and deals additional damage. The chance of a magical surge increases each time this cantrip’s damage increases at higher levels.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e350658g92b2g40abg4e13g0a0194995e34" version="1">Arcane Vigor</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd4a4e4dg3a3eg0bd1g2716gc7e32738a35f" version="1">You tap into your life force to heal yourself.</content>
  <content contentuid="h20d548d9g2600gaf44geda5gd71ed6825255" version="1">Magical Cunning</content>
  <content contentuid="h0475c80dgb3d2g65a0g32e3g51e0604b9fae" version="1">You can perform an esoteric rite for 1 minute. At the end of it, you regain expended Pact Magic spell slots but no more than a number equal to half your maximum (round up). Once you use this feature, you can’t do so again until you finish a Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbe38acefg243eg2454ge187g5d1c50d4bb2b" version="2">Level 1: Eldritch Mind</content>
  <content contentuid="h9958bcb7g9126g6467g3b95g0f07e49ea19d" version="1">You have Advantage on Constitution saving throws that you make to maintain Concentration.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha12d8231ga51ag15b0gaa53g6e00282dc4a2" version="1">Level 1: Pact of the Blade</content>
  <content contentuid="he1bd3e3eg338fg58d5g3de3g9be05e9302e7" version="1">Level 1: Pact of the Chain</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e2924dag8101gd3b2g68a2g6add03aed4dd" version="1">Level 1: Pact of the Tome</content>
  <content contentuid="h25396b5dgdf7bg8d51g09d5g87f669d3be25" version="1">Level 1: Armour of Shadows</content>
  <content contentuid="h25cfc459ge325g3d22g7037g9a95573234b1" version="1">Level 2: Agonising Blast</content>
  <content contentuid="h56007d5dgf3f2gc9c2g10eegc2fef230c9e6" version="1">Level 2: Devil's Sight</content>
  <content contentuid="hf94f288fge015g4a15g6c34g367d15c45d89" version="1">Level 2: Eldritch Spear</content>
  <content contentuid="hc803f28bg3024g3fd8gc979gbeb1263f4991" version="1">Level 2: Mask of Many Faces</content>
  <content contentuid="ha97e7097gda9cgc3eegbb86g9bf88d36ee68" version="1">Level 2: Otherworldly Leap</content>
  <content contentuid="hd47c4e1cg1e7ag651cg8c57g7deb405ec80c" version="1">Level 2: Repelling Blast</content>
  <content contentuid="h425487e0g16b7ga256gb63ag56872a5ea672" version="1">Level 5: Eldritch Smite</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d483577g0d77g722dg50ddga9f231b29ec2" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc0ad688dged59g744fgf3e6g1e706f4ee29c" version="1">Level 5: One with Shadows</content>
  <content contentuid="hb2501172gdfd6gb7ebg0621ga38a34e3f573" version="1">Level 5: Thirsting Blade</content>
  <content contentuid="ha794dab4gf433ga08bg7d82gda68964c691c" version="1">You gain the Extra Attack feature for your pact weapon only. With that feature, you can attack twice with the weapon instead of once when you take the Attack action on your turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c1dba3ag239egef50g0d52g47241e4e6016" version="1">Level 5: Investment of the Chain Master</content>
  <content contentuid="he5f3196agc9ccg5177gedd9ged594f4d1f5a" version="1">Level 5: Gift of the Depths</content>
  <content contentuid="h307a5339gff1ag9485g5387gfb0813a818b3" version="1">Level 7: Whispers of the Grave</content>
  <content contentuid="hd7310e4agc213gc092gf6fag5e8c8130b34d" version="1">Level 9: Gift of the Protectors</content>
  <content contentuid="h87d4e985gc3a3g6b66g2385g07e2b48896df" version="1">You can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_DeathWard"&gt;Death Ward&lt;/LSTag&gt; without expending a &lt;LSTag Tooltip="SpellSlot"&gt;spell slot&lt;/LSTag&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd84b885bge9e8g3573gd4ffg49076a30df65" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 2+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="hecbef4dfg8243g14d6g9693gac003507a80f" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 2+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c66be28g9561g15fcg3b9dga1250371427d" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 2+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h5998bc9cg0a28g94afg1a59g5ef2c18cef61" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 2+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d4bd307g5d48gebb2g299bg828ff537fd3c" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 2+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h35ea3bedgaf6dg4319gd657g95569aedae04" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 2+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h284ddfa3g663ag50c2g07e9g9ac8fe753bcd" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock, Pact of the Blade Invocation</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c37c62dg8f18g4212gc85fgb76c2c9723ec" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d4f86adg3e6fg113dg666fg926e6f0083ba" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock, Pact of the Blade Invocation</content>
  <content contentuid="hde2d1489gd4e5gf6f4g63e9g804d8eb5d149" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 7+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="ha94435d8g091cgce68gaca4gc20e3eea7844" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock, Pact of the Chain Invocation</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c3434c5ge1cfg2712gf301g25080935ac60" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock, Pact of the Tome Invocation</content>
  <content contentuid="h79064293gdc22g33fcgf577g81a7411a9720" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 9+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="hb8aec518g6d45g1454g58cbgbac23fec6617" version="1">Level 9: Lifedrinker</content>
  <content contentuid="h35551526g84e1g78f3g1277g241f3a6077bb" version="2">Once per turn, when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can deal an extra 1d6 Necrotic damage to that creature. You also regain a number of Hit Points equal to 1d6 plus your Constitution modifier.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb7444fe8g6554g6a31ged37g03cc050ef8d3" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 9+ Warlock, Pact of the Blade Invocation</content>
  <content contentuid="hd69af339g9d2bg91b6gba38g8dbeb8503f7b" version="1">Level 12: Devouring Blade</content>
  <content contentuid="haf78a66bg2f9bg5fb7g8c9ag5da07aa459f4" version="1">The Extra Attack of your Thirsting Blade invocation confers two extra attacks rather than one.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc579ca24g72d1g35dfg46c5g5274d47b30cc" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 12+ Warlock, Thirsting Blade Invocation</content>
  <content contentuid="h007cf464gd375gf74bg38ccgdc14ddbc38cf" version="1">Level 1: Beast Speech</content>
  <content contentuid="h0f9d1ae5g4592g2f49gb8c7g87c552837f15" version="1">Level 1: Beguiling Influence</content>
  <content contentuid="h6657b78egb581g0244g06feg115830c4d5fe" version="1">Level 2: Thief of Five Fates</content>
  <content contentuid="h96b23ed5g9f6eg5ed9gc731gf83643845844" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 2+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="hda228a0eg1468g0defg7675gfa912f042658" version="1">Level 5: Mire the Mind</content>
  <content contentuid="h8dd81e23g9a97gc012g10f6g34aea3e1b3be" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="hdb88100cgafa2g940ag4433gb000edb33a07" version="1">Level 5: Sign of Ill Omen</content>
  <content contentuid="h1b7fb0eag8d29g4cf4g04fag91b2e056cf0c" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="hda504259gf2e4g3266g40fdge92c642b1182" version="1">Level 5: Book of Ancient Secrets</content>
  <content contentuid="hdc954407ge07fg170agc027gb3ac7e6afda9" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 5+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h0738ad5cg28e2g4092gfc87gc94c75bc8f5b" version="1">Level 7: Dreadful Word</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e82dd96g79f2g67a9g365dgc089cab1b728" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 7+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h1fb30dc3ge20dgcb22g34d0gcdd0e387793b" version="1">Level 7: Sculptor of Flesh</content>
  <content contentuid="hd6f07d39ge321g7e13gcdabgbcbf12aaa406" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 7+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h5ebc0953g6724g72fageab4g7f5682f9fb32" version="1">Level 9: Minions of Chaos</content>
  <content contentuid="hf1a63187g9766gc5aeg0b86g693324a45025" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 9+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h3098d03bg9b76gd04eg7ef8g689022ec62ad" version="1">Invocation: Gift of the Protectors</content>
  <content contentuid="had9ee1e5g5369g47b5g65c4g37b956523a59" version="1">Mind Sliver</content>
  <content contentuid="h3f49f302g9b29g72f7g25f0g2f3ff3297c48" version="1">You try to temporarily sliver the mind of one creature you can see within range. The target must succeed on an Intelligence saving throw or take Psychic damage and subtract 1d4 from the next saving throw it makes before the end of your next turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1be8ef4cg573bg9247g8bf7gbe003418678b" version="1">Warlock cantrips that deal damage and have a range have their range increased by 1.5 times when you cast them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h92b0f41cg7222g57a1gf293g5f9b67f6c76a" version="1">Warlock cantrips that require an attack roll: when you hit a Large or smaller creature with such a cantrip, you can push the creature up to [1] directly away from you.</content>
  <content contentuid="h63854322g2981gf688g3b17g3be3eb3cbaea" version="1">Eldritch Blast</content>
  <content contentuid="h5821657eg6a48gdd10gb380ga906788793a5" version="1">Conjure [1] beam(s) of crackling energy.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha82b5e6dgb4b1gb2a1g8b53g475515ffec20" version="1">Booming Blade</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e37672dgdb7bg5838g12bcg8e96a88d3d98" version="1">Strike with your weapon, afflicting your foe with a resonance that hurts them for [1] when they move.</content>
  <content contentuid="hde7eade7g981dg355bg6e30g0089c6fe0377" version="1">True Strike (Melee)</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc5b991fgffcdgbc3bgbe4eg4bbb47637ce8" version="1">Guided by a flash of magical insight, you make one attack with the weapon used in the spell’s casting. The attack uses your spellcasting ability for the attack and damage rolls instead of using Strength or Dexterity. If the attack deals damage, it is Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc48575fbg3411gc50ag88aeg18f05fb53a0f" version="1">True Strike (Ranged)</content>
  <content contentuid="he4de88abg8ba4g6afeg8c45g9069fad18699" version="1">Guided by a flash of magical insight, you make one attack with the weapon used in the spell’s casting. The attack uses your spellcasting ability for the attack and damage rolls instead of using Strength or Dexterity. If the attack deals damage, it is Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h573020b3g1241g8748g5cccgf1a7c580e5d4" version="1">Guided by a flash of magical insight, you make one attack with the weapon used in the spell’s casting. The attack uses your spellcasting ability for the attack and damage rolls instead of using Strength or Dexterity. If the attack deals damage, it is Radiant damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h17b4c239g8209gd0fbg57b8gadfb6d1e2826" version="1">Your &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_FindFamiliar"&gt;familiar&lt;/LSTag&gt; gains an Extra Attack.</content>
  <content contentuid="h170d4635g2a45gd51dg6f7cg0cc6d58ae805" version="1">You can cast &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_AnimateDead"&gt;Animate Dead&lt;/LSTag&gt;, &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_Haste"&gt;Haste&lt;/LSTag&gt;, and &lt;LSTag Type="Spell" Tooltip="Target_CallLightning"&gt;Call Lightning&lt;/LSTag&gt; once each per Long Rest.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1b185049g69f6gd479g03c1g85c564525648" version="1">Eldritch Smite</content>
  <content contentuid="h3793d1a6gc4b8g72a7geb63gdab6620030e7" version="1">Eldritch Smite</content>
  <content contentuid="h39dbb752g7bd1g7b6fgad55gb007b398ba91" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="h96af7feag9483ge79egf274ga41eefe9ae04" version="1">Eldritch Smite</content>
  <content contentuid="h94488385g3579gb95bga59ag7e9114cbe4d1" version="1">Eldritch Smite: Reaction</content>
  <content contentuid="hecfe0232g690bg7d4cg4846gf2a7cf8ec8c8" version="1">Eldritch Smite: Reaction</content>
  <content contentuid="hadfb9c0egff7fgfa1eg62abgf89d0d720111" version="1">Eldritch Smite: Reaction</content>
  <content contentuid="h90aeb23egee85gab21g41b9g52b42e64cb53" version="1">Eldritch Smite: Reaction</content>
  <content contentuid="h736c0facgf8fdg1f25g787bg0dc22143c55e" version="1">Eldritch Smite: Reaction</content>
  <content contentuid="hccbfc687g197cgaf11g2e5cg2aa9a4c51ef2" version="1">Eldritch Smite: Reaction</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b469932gb9a1gf6f4gdaa5g2804016be6b3" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2ed3d6d2g203agef73ge378g989ea6dc9107" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1e4fce8gbccbg813cgdb6bgcf29cb502ca1" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2fae1edegb1eege388gf87cg39ad6381ae22" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c6eccdeg66d4g0163gd637g573e9b7a1610" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="h801bf2a6g08cfgac63gc48fgdc1a93297403" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="heb8d0bd4gf518g09cbgdf04g875209dd858a" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd23c4cc6g5a99gc62eg7220ge0f7cee47aba" version="1">Once per turn when you hit a creature with your pact weapon, you can expend a Pact Magic spell slot to deal an extra 1d8 Force damage to the target, plus another 1d8 per level of the spell slot, and you can give the target the Prone condition if it is Huge or smaller.</content>
  <content contentuid="h24650f10g65f0gdad5g30cdg3e4777297c7c" version="1">Level 2: Scholar</content>
  <content contentuid="h32ed567egee36g91e1g2accgb992c0f4d730" version="1">While studying magic, you also specialized in another field of study. Choose one of the following skills in which you have proficiency: Arcana, History, Investigation, Medicine, Nature, or Religion. You have Expertise in the chosen skill.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f5671feg10a3g6221g9db1gcd1af3a88f5b" version="1">Level 2: Expertise</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e315a90g0705gb2c6g1a8eg13de362924de" version="1">You gain Expertise (see the rules glossary) in two of your skill proficiencies of your choice. Performance and Persuasion are recommended if you have proficiency in them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Bard level 9, you gain Expertise in two more of your skill proficiencies of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1d573d0cg0ef8gc58cg5d87gf7b0ce7fc23d" version="1">Level 10: Magical Secrets</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5715a4dge184g890agee7ag4f904fb90c6b" version="1">You’ve learned secrets from various magical traditions. Whenever you reach a Bard level (including this level) and the Prepared Spells number in the Bard Features table increases, you can choose any of your new prepared spells from the Bard, Cleric, Druid, and Wizard spell lists, and the chosen spells count as Bard spells for you (see a class’s section for its spell list). In addition, whenever you replace a spell prepared for this class, you can replace it with a spell from those lists.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd4f3b039g6204g1bbagd21fgb72f806b54d8" version="1">Level 3: Combat Inspiration</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0e61f8bg955fgda33g3e08gc99c259c8a16" version="1">Level 3: Blessings of Knowledge</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9341211ge6c1g1fd9gddbeg13315817fedb" version="1">You gain proficiency in two of the following skills of your choice: Arcana, History, Nature, or Religion. You have Expertise in those two skills.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha8b64524g7467g0f1eg9214gbd3da8ce6302" version="1">Level 1: Expertise</content>
  <content contentuid="h75d54fe5g6285g141fgd2b8gca722e196ecc" version="1">You gain Expertise in two of your skill proficiencies of your choice. Sleight of Hand and Stealth are recommended if you have proficiency in them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At Rogue level 6, you gain Expertise in two more of your skill proficiencies of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="hac07bd19g5886gc2efgf8dfgb838d23ca0bd" version="1">Level 5: Cunning Strike</content>
  <content contentuid="h4c3e9164gb5c2g35d0g405dgb887921e3e3a" version="1">You’ve developed cunning ways to use your Sneak Attack. When you deal Sneak Attack damage, you can add one of the following Cunning Strike effects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If a Cunning Strike effect requires a saving throw, the DC equals 8 plus your Dexterity modifier and Proficiency Bonus.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d4d8d0bgd8f1g3ea1g0101ga6595c40a70f" version="1">Cunning Strike: Poison</content>
  <content contentuid="h88c13810gba24gc873gb1c9ge3c3fe8cb917" version="2">You add a toxin to your strike, forcing the target to make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, the target has the Poisoned condition for 1 minute. At the end of each of its turns, the Poisoned target repeats the save, ending the effect on itself on a success.</content>
  <content contentuid="h14896c14gd1f3gead8g4a00g37ead89aa9ae" version="1">Cunning Strike: Trip</content>
  <content contentuid="h4642fa9fg99f2g37fcg659cg1f43f42e73ee" version="1">If the target is Large or smaller, it must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or have the Prone condition.</content>
  <content contentuid="hceff31b1g6ebfg0d4cg2043g91b11847623c" version="1">Cunning Strike: Withdraw</content>
  <content contentuid="h490512eagca8bg6208g723cg27ee0882906d" version="1">Immediately after the attack, you move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="he11ccf69g4145g3cbfg6094gf14d8136626c" version="1">Withdraw</content>
  <content contentuid="h1ef2156age1a2ge866g5ac5g338e62d3da81" version="1">Immediately after the attack, you move up to half your Speed without provoking Opportunity Attacks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3952e016gc549gd27fgc618ga417ad5120c1" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 1+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="he0d8fa8bgadb5g8c7fga076gbec7aa4441cb" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 1+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h30fd69d5ge1a6gda26g435dgb055ede6ab30" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 1+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h9216324dgcc3bg6778ga40aga3796b155c0c" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 1+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h29e638a5g9fe4gca09gb884g608413f8e11f" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 1+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h74e5b82bg3e1eg42d0g108ag8296ce9e9f59" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 1+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="h89cc571cg9734g0e75g9d8fg69ec4116823f" version="1">Prerequisite: Level 1+ Warlock</content>
  <content contentuid="hda66831fg300fg893ega428gd807bb12f766" version="1">Acolyte</content>
  <content contentuid="h18021532g7cf1g263eg148bg852a52db6cf5" version="1">You have spent your life in service to a temple, learning sacred rites and providing sacrifices to the god or gods you worship. Serving the gods and discovering their sacred works will guide you to greatness.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd660fd06g45aeg25f4g7e9dg6fd338c66f83" version="1">Origin Feat: Magic Initiate (Cleric)</content>
  <content contentuid="ha980b3fbg98dcgc88eg9edbg89be32a4b191" version="2">Magic Initiate (Cleric): Cantrip</content>
  <content contentuid="hd57d4d53gfb82gc5e5ge39eg18ccf99d11ac" version="1">Magic Initiate (Cleric): Cantrip 2</content>
  <content contentuid="hee720882g4ca7g0c82g0f6dgda96a14a144e" version="2">Cantrip learning mode is active. All Cleric cantrips are added to your spell list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you cast a cantrip, you permanently learn that cantrip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After selecting two different cantrips, this mode ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7d1ae2c1g95b6g5a3dgc067g1baf8491753f" version="2">Cantrip learning mode is active. All Cleric cantrips are added to your spell list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you cast a cantrip, you permanently learn that cantrip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After selecting two different cantrips, this mode ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="he64b4a45gba6eg30a6g9703gb0f13f9230e8" version="1">Magic Initiate (Cleric): Cantrip</content>
  <content contentuid="hd21b5377g2221gaafdga39bgea72f3a697d1" version="1">Magic Initiate (Druid): Cantrip</content>
  <content contentuid="h3522b895gaf8eg23c8ge2a5g19305a3832ce" version="1">Origin Feat: Magic Initiate (Druid)</content>
  <content contentuid="h3be2808fgdf36g2f49g651dgd7072fe1c369" version="1">Magic Initiate (Druid): Cantrip</content>
  <content contentuid="hcf7beb3cg8662gd7d0ga3aag9f047d9b8897" version="1">Magic Initiate (Wizard): Cantrip</content>
  <content contentuid="h7fd3e98dg8cddgd47cg0aeag9f03355feaaa" version="1">Two Cantrips. You learn two cantrips of your choice from the Cleric, Druid, or Wizard spell lists. When you select this feat, choose Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma as your spellcasting ability for these spells.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Level 1 Spell. Choose one 1st-level spell from the same list you selected for your cantrips. You always have this spell prepared, and you gain one 1st-level spell slot to cast it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb18213feg1443g46dfg66c8g43152a53cf75" version="2">Cantrip learning mode is active. All Druid cantrips are added to your spell list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you cast a cantrip, you permanently learn that cantrip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After selecting two different cantrips, this mode ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd31cacc2g7f81g20c3gc487gec7d06e97e53" version="2">Cantrip learning mode is active. All Wizard cantrips are added to your spell list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you cast a cantrip, you permanently learn that cantrip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After selecting two different cantrips, this mode ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="h948ef541g3485gbf64g5f3ag0b03af06a06a" version="1">Magic Initiate (Cleric): Spell</content>
  <content contentuid="h0452adf6gbffcga716g8490gdad124c18bb6" version="2">Spell learning mode is active. All Cleric spells are added to your spell list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you cast a spell, you permanently learn that spell.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After selecting a spell, this mode ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1a2947cg6d72g0cb9g22eagc5ff105e4237" version="1">Magic Initiate (Druid): Spell</content>
  <content contentuid="he3771dbcg23f0g570dg2d5egf79cec30d589" version="2">Spell learning mode is active. All Druid spells are added to your spell list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you cast a spell, you permanently learn that spell.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After selecting a spell, this mode ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc6335af1g4129g0308g8518g3cb980ec4a55" version="1">Magic Initiate (Wizard): Spell</content>
  <content contentuid="hffa4fb6cg516eg4f17g0656geecaebcd5045" version="2">Spell learning mode is active. All Wizard spells are added to your spell list.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you cast a spell, you permanently learn that spell.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After selecting a spell, this mode ends.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb75003cbgf00cga299gd802g14c70c5d2869" version="1">Charlatan</content>
  <content contentuid="hcc3c36c6gd341g9ef3g75a6gd57375a199cd" version="1">You're an expert in manipulation, prone to exaggeration and more than happy to profit from it. Bending the truth and turning allies against each other will lead to greater success down the road.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4b835e70g04c6g5a06g0c6dg1a3127667686" version="1">Criminal</content>
  <content contentuid="hbcaf83c9gb788g62e0g6965g3fa62228f254" version="1">You have a history of breaking the law and survive by leveraging less-than-legal connections. Profiting from criminal enterprise will lead to greater opportunities in the future.</content>
  <content contentuid="h71130c00gf7fegc295g7a78g226b23bab525" version="1">Entertainer</content>
  <content contentuid="h2716640cg5333g5237g4376g52bc2bce3db6" version="1">You live to sway and subvert your audience, engaging common crowds and high society alike. Preserving art and bringing joy to the hapless and downtrodden heightens your charismatic aura.</content>
  <content contentuid="h08144bfegc7fbg3b4cg2a08gf4711304db2f" version="1">Folk Hero</content>
  <content contentuid="h16aa023egdc3cg5bc2g7476g71950aebff42" version="1">You're a champion of the common people, challenging tyrants and monsters to protect the helpless. Saving innocents in imminent danger will make your legend grow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8872efb5g9022g184cg8400gc8622021c434" version="1">Guild Artisan</content>
  <content contentuid="hecaca218g03ebge2e3g1541g30dab1f4df21" version="1">Your skill in a particular craft has earned you membership in a mercantile guild, offering privileges and protection while engaging in your art. Repairing and discovering rare crafts will bring new inspiration.</content>
  <content contentuid="h68877c75g37c1gbf22gf33fg60fb10459cda" version="1">Noble</content>
  <content contentuid="h11a3cb02g94efge2aagfd7eg2559e2181833" version="1">You were raised in a family among the social elite, accustomed to power and privilege. Accumulating renown, power, and loyalty will raise your status.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdffa4c4fgb9e6g20ebg7a88g407a2ca29c32" version="1">Outlander</content>
  <content contentuid="h5039598cg6db2g2d04g6e52gb5d4956c7773" version="1">You grew up in the wilds, learning to survive far from the comforts of civilisation. Surviving unusual hazards of the wild will enhance your prowess and understanding.</content>
  <content contentuid="h95a25eaegdeafgb7b8g4801g7a8367fc65a7" version="1">Sage</content>
  <content contentuid="hca28ebc2ga938g8c68g1dbag7edf639c41fc" version="1">You are curious and well-read, with an unending thirst for knowledge. Learning about rare lore of the world will inspire you to put this knowledge to greater purpose.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8109bc16gabcag925cgdd47gb46dba14be0c" version="1">Soldier</content>
  <content contentuid="hc868035bgcc3dg4f6ag8137g0a3e325b8ba7" version="1">You are trained in battlefield tactics and combat, having served in a militia, mercenary company, or officer corps. Show smart tactics and bravery on the battlefield to enhance your prowess.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc87a3f0fgaf2eg6057g69fbg9ba7b0e2f7bb" version="1">Urchin</content>
  <content contentuid="h9f4e80c6g4dd1gb652gbb63g04b844b503ae" version="1">After surviving a poor and bleak childhood, you know how to make the most out of very little. Using your street smarts bolsters your spirit for the journey ahead.</content>
  <content contentuid="h15a25456g93c5g2128g2199gd75ca7acd724" version="1">Origin Feat: Skilled</content>
  <content contentuid="h9c4f90acg7e1cg80f9g49b9g223423a07c77" version="1">You gain proficiency in any combination of three skills or tools of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0b1ce19fg660ag4802g476bg8c05a68222d8" version="1">Skilled: Acrobatics</content>
  <content contentuid="h0c81c67cgb4c6g4561g00beg5a12ada00691" version="1">Skilled: Animal Handling</content>
  <content contentuid="h29993998g99bdg851dg0dccgdbf3b1370e56" version="1">Skilled: Arcana</content>
  <content contentuid="h0fa6c280g9e87g0644g135bg21f0cdf93433" version="1">Skilled: Athletics</content>
  <content contentuid="hfbd6a1b1g89fag83a8g0e7ege0255b94efda" version="1">Skilled: Deception</content>
  <content contentuid="h90eb1d04g6929gc5d6gea2ag4c14b8d10050" version="1">Skilled: History</content>
  <content contentuid="h2493bc3cgd699g2700g7ba2g908cbedeae7a" version="1">Skilled: Insight</content>
  <content contentuid="h4466962dg5878ge4ddg2288gbc90cd13da1b" version="1">Skilled: Intimidation</content>
  <content contentuid="h97ae1233gb416g9366g5de6g48653fa24df6" version="1">Skilled: Investigation</content>
  <content contentuid="h34cec7c2g780cg0070g2be3gfc093346a1ef" version="1">Skilled: Medicine</content>
  <content contentuid="hada03c6fg8b80g6cfbg761eg6ec6542cc0a5" version="1">Skilled: Nature</content>
  <content contentuid="h8521f637ga957g4fdeg40bbg3e8514ee2243" version="1">Skilled: Perception</content>
  <content contentuid="h3644d11cg3f56gfa05g9d01g8c44cbf8f993" version="1">Skilled: Performance</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e284e1cg7a31g63cag5ccegeaa125cdbdf0" version="1">Skilled: Persuasion</content>
  <content contentuid="hceae7ad3gf0dbgdd24gcc1bg7bd21312fc0a" version="1">Skilled: Religion</content>
  <content contentuid="hc931f53agbc8egb132g41cdg19cd166d6f7b" version="1">Skilled: Sleight of Hand</content>
  <content contentuid="h9eb6dc6dg1471g2dbcg9f1bgee4b610efd55" version="1">Skilled: Stealth</content>
  <content contentuid="hb990e3c4g5425g1524gfedcg5f20ce20597d" version="1">Skilled: Survival</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f8e4f76g9279geaf4g3be8g75fcc8975180" version="1">Skilled</content>
  <content contentuid="ha89bce32gf8a8g61a1gda37gae4076b0817a" version="1">You gain proficiency in any combination of three skills of your choice.</content>
  <content contentuid="haccfb564g42d5gbcf1g17e3g6bd3bb113a44" version="1">Acrobatics</content>
  <content contentuid="hc355df2ag0123g443bg998cg11187bf11a5a" version="1">AnimalHandling</content>
  <content contentuid="h722b6a69g3477g36dbg1e4fg04643c68b1f7" version="1">Arcana</content>
  <content contentuid="h5329602dgbdb7gdf54g164cg7babc0547f88" version="1">Athletics</content>
  <content contentuid="h4a18bdbcg2f07g8fc3ga383g3bf38d934d97" version="1">Deception</content>
  <content contentuid="h15608410g73bagc53bg53f2ga41d7d3b2f96" version="1">History</content>
  <content contentuid="h41367f77g2252gf46bg7c6bge19d48c4f278" version="1">Nature</content>
  <content contentuid="h459ce53fg7791g1cd0g378eg2c1353e49c4f" version="1">Perception</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b423612ge7e5g8736gd607g7c134dc79c3a" version="1">Performance</content>
  <content contentuid="hdc9b288fg9711g7a53gfe81g9448c4523a2c" version="1">Persuasion</content>
  <content contentuid="h57eaf745g2783g5cc4gc9f6gd12380a0934f" version="1">Religion</content>
  <content contentuid="h87e650ddg0175gc7f8g135eg826bd05429d2" version="1">SleightOfHand</content>
  <content contentuid="h237ebf10g65d4g5de2ga9f8g4aeae8f52710" version="1">Stealth</content>
  <content contentuid="hcaedae0bg8d89g5535gef15ge3bead7cac7b" version="1">Survival</content>
  <content contentuid="h96a2be22g2936g6b20g8c6fga91b0ccaa06d" version="1">Insight</content>
  <content contentuid="h4107cf58gb2cdgcf41g08c5gcb3b1ab720a4" version="1">Intimidation</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ba0cf67g55f2ge128g4fefg499a17387298" version="1">Investigation</content>
  <content contentuid="h58264943ge8a3g47cdg09c2gd71af9051c26" version="1">Medicine</content>
  <content contentuid="h5ec953edgae89gbe4fgbc37g46d66f973083" version="1">You have gained proficiency in the skill.</content>
</contentList>